<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
   <teiHeader>
      <fileDesc>
         <titleStmt>
            <title>A ready vvay to remember the Scriptures. Or, A table of the Old and Nevv Testament. By that late able, painfull, and worthy man of God, Ezekiel Culuervvell, minister of the Word</title>
            <author>Culverwell, Ezekiel, 1553 or 4-1631.</author>
         </titleStmt>
         <editionStmt>
            <edition>
               <date>1637</date>
            </edition>
         </editionStmt>
         <extent>Approx. 166 KB of XML-encoded text transcribed from 48 1-bit group-IV TIFF page images.</extent>
         <publicationStmt>
            <publisher>Text Creation Partnership,</publisher>
            <pubPlace>Ann Arbor, MI ; Oxford (UK) :</pubPlace>
            <date when="2014-11">2014-11 (EEBO-TCP Phase 2).</date>
            <idno type="DLPS">A19692</idno>
            <idno type="STC">STC 6111</idno>
            <idno type="STC">ESTC S109129</idno>
            <idno type="EEBO-CITATION">99844779</idno>
            <idno type="PROQUEST">99844779</idno>
            <idno type="VID">9621</idno>
            <availability>
               <p>To the extent possible under law, the Text Creation Partnership has waived all copyright and related or neighboring rights to this keyboarded and encoded edition of the work described above, according to the terms of the CC0 1.0 Public Domain Dedication (http://creativecommons.org/publicdomain/zero/1.0/). This waiver does not extend to any page images or other supplementary files associated with this work, which may be protected by copyright or other license restrictions. Please go to https://www.textcreationpartnership.org/ for more information about the project.</p>
            </availability>
         </publicationStmt>
         <seriesStmt>
            <title>Early English books online text creation partnership.</title>
         </seriesStmt>
         <notesStmt>
            <note>(EEBO-TCP ; phase 2, no. A19692)</note>
            <note>Transcribed from: (Early English Books Online ; image set 9621)</note>
            <note>Images scanned from microfilm: (Early English books, 1475-1640 ; 1199:11)</note>
         </notesStmt>
         <sourceDesc>
            <biblFull>
               <titleStmt>
                  <title>A ready vvay to remember the Scriptures. Or, A table of the Old and Nevv Testament. By that late able, painfull, and worthy man of God, Ezekiel Culuervvell, minister of the Word</title>
                  <author>Culverwell, Ezekiel, 1553 or 4-1631.</author>
               </titleStmt>
               <extent>[4], 76, 79-94 p.   </extent>
               <publicationStmt>
                  <publisher>Printed by Iohn Clark, and are to bee sold at his shop vnder St. Peters Church in Cornhill,</publisher>
                  <pubPlace>London :</pubPlace>
                  <date>1637.</date>
               </publicationStmt>
               <notesStmt>
                  <note>Reproduction of the original in the Henry E. Huntington Library and Art Gallery.</note>
               </notesStmt>
            </biblFull>
         </sourceDesc>
      </fileDesc>
      <encodingDesc>
         <projectDesc>
            <p>Created by converting TCP files to TEI P5 using tcp2tei.xsl,
      TEI @ Oxford.
      </p>
         </projectDesc>
         <editorialDecl>
            <p>EEBO-TCP is a partnership between the Universities of Michigan and Oxford and the publisher ProQuest to create accurately transcribed and encoded texts based on the image sets published by ProQuest via their Early English Books Online (EEBO) database (http://eebo.chadwyck.com). The general aim of EEBO-TCP is to encode one copy (usually the first edition) of every monographic English-language title published between 1473 and 1700 available in EEBO.</p>
            <p>EEBO-TCP aimed to produce large quantities of textual data within the usual project restraints of time and funding, and therefore chose to create diplomatic transcriptions (as opposed to critical editions) with light-touch, mainly structural encoding based on the Text Encoding Initiative (http://www.tei-c.org).</p>
            <p>The EEBO-TCP project was divided into two phases. The 25,368 texts created during Phase 1 of the project (2000-2009), initially available only to institutions that contributed to their creation, were released into the public domain on 1 January 2015. The approximately 40,000 texts produced during Phase 2 (2009- ), of which 34,963 had been released as of 2020, originally similarly restricted, were similarly freed from all restrictions on 1 August 2020. As of that date anyone is free to take and use these texts for any purpose (modify them, annotate them, distribute them, etc.). But we do respectfully request that due credit and attribution be given to their original source.</p>
            <p>Users should be aware of the process of creating the TCP texts, and therefore of any assumptions that can be made about the data.</p>
            <p>Text selection was based on the New Cambridge Bibliography of English Literature (NCBEL). If an author (or for an anonymous work, the title) appears in NCBEL, then their works are eligible for inclusion. Selection was intended to range over a wide variety of subject areas, to reflect the true nature of the print record of the period. In general, first editions of a works in English were prioritized, although there are a number of works in other languages, notably Latin and Welsh, included and sometimes a second or later edition of a work was chosen if there was a compelling reason to do so.</p>
            <p>Image sets were sent to external keying companies for transcription and basic encoding. Quality assurance was then carried out by editorial teams in Oxford and Michigan. 5% (or 5 pages, whichever is the greater) of each text was proofread for accuracy and those which did not meet QA standards were returned to the keyers to be redone. After proofreading, the encoding was enhanced and/or corrected and characters marked as illegible were corrected where possible up to a limit of 100 instances per text. Any remaining illegibles were encoded as &lt;gap&gt;s. Understanding these processes should make clear that, while the overall quality of TCP data is very good, some errors will remain and some readable characters will be marked as illegible. Users should bear in mind that in all likelihood such instances will never have been looked at by a TCP editor.</p>
            <p>The texts were encoded and linked to page images in accordance with level 4 of the TEI in Libraries guidelines.</p>
            <p>Copies of the texts have been issued variously as SGML (TCP schema; ASCII text with mnemonic sdata character entities); displayable XML (TCP schema; characters represented either as UTF-8 Unicode or text strings within braces); or lossless XML (TEI P5, characters represented either as UTF-8 Unicode or TEI g elements).</p>
            <p>Keying and markup guidelines are available at the <ref target="http://www.textcreationpartnership.org/docs/.">Text Creation Partnership web site</ref>.</p>
         </editorialDecl>
         <listPrefixDef>
            <prefixDef ident="tcp"
                       matchPattern="([0-9\-]+):([0-9IVX]+)"
                       replacementPattern="http://eebo.chadwyck.com/downloadtiff?vid=$1&amp;page=$2"/>
            <prefixDef ident="char"
                       matchPattern="(.+)"
                       replacementPattern="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/textcreationpartnership/Texts/master/tcpchars.xml#$1"/>
         </listPrefixDef>
      </encodingDesc>
      <profileDesc>
         <langUsage>
            <language ident="eng">eng</language>
         </langUsage>
         <textClass>
            <keywords scheme="http://authorities.loc.gov/">
               <term>Bible --  Outlines, syllabi, etc. --  Early works to 1800.</term>
            </keywords>
         </textClass>
      </profileDesc>
      <revisionDesc>
         <change>
            <date>2013-07</date>
            <label>TCP</label>Assigned for keying and markup</change>
         <change>
            <date>2013-08</date>
            <label>SPi Global</label>Keyed and coded from ProQuest page images</change>
         <change>
            <date>2013-11</date>
            <label>Ali Jakobson</label>Sampled and proofread</change>
         <change>
            <date>2013-11</date>
            <label>Ali Jakobson</label>Text and markup reviewed and edited</change>
         <change>
            <date>2014-03</date>
            <label>pfs</label>Batch review (QC) and XML conversion</change>
      </revisionDesc>
   </teiHeader>
   <text xml:lang="eng">
      <front>
         <div type="title_page">
            <pb facs="tcp:9621:1"/>
            <pb facs="tcp:9621:1" rendition="simple:additions"/>
            <p>A READY WAY TO REMEMBER THE <hi>SCRIPT<g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>RES.</hi> OR, A TABLE OF THE OLD <hi>and</hi> NEVV TESTAMENT.</p>
            <p>BY That late able, painfull, and wor<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>thy man of God, EZEKIEL CVLVERVVELL, <hi>Miniſter of the Word.</hi>
            </p>
            <p>LONDON, Printed for IOHN CLARK, and are to bee ſold at his Shop vnder S<hi rend="sup">r</hi>. <hi>Peters</hi> Church in <hi>Cornhill.</hi> 1637.</p>
         </div>
         <div type="to_the_reader">
            <pb facs="tcp:9621:2"/>
            <pb facs="tcp:9621:2"/>
            <head>TO THE READER.</head>
            <p>
               <seg rend="decorInit">H</seg>Aving many yeares agoe gathe<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>red and made this briefe Col<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lection of all the principall mat<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ters contained in the <hi>New Teſtament,</hi> whereby I may ſay (I loſt not my labour) for I found it by good Experience no ſmall helpe vnto me; for by it I could eaſily finde any principall matter; Now although the chiefe vſe thereof be for Divines and young Stu<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dents, yet vpon the deſire of many good Chriſtians, which have found the like fruit and benefit, I was willing to publiſh the ſame and make it more com<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mon; vnto whom I wiſh, that reading over the New Teſtament, they diligently obſerve the contents and chiefe matter contained in every Chapter and Verſe, and often repeat them over, and every day to goe thorow ſome Chapter or other; and the bet<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ter
<pb facs="tcp:9621:3"/> to keepe the Contents in memorie, to ſay over daily that which is paſt; wherby I have good proofe, that by this meanes, in ſhort time one may readily tell what are the Contents of any Chapter, and where any ſpeciall matter is written, (which I conceive may be a good Exerciſe for the trayning vp of Chil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dren of tenne yeares old and vpward) for by reading over theſe Contents, a man well exerciſed in the Scriptures, may is one houre ſee the principall mat<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ters in the whole <hi>New Teſtament:</hi> One ſpeciall vſe thereof will be this<g ref="char:punc">▪</g> to fill the Head, and ſo the Heart, with much heavenly matter, which is the beſt way to keepe out idle thoughts. And therefore now having my hearts deſire in what I did expect, I have thought good to publiſh the like on the <hi>Old Teſta<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ment.</hi> For direction I need not ſay much, for it is eaſily perceived, that the Figures at the beginning of each line, ſtands for the Chapter, and the figures following the words, for the Verſe.</p>
            <closer>
               <signed>E. C.</signed>
            </closer>
         </div>
      </front>
      <body>
         <div type="table">
            <pb n="1" facs="tcp:9621:3"/>
            <head>A TABLE OF THE OLD TESTAMENT.</head>
            <list>
               <head>GENESIS.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1. <seg rend="decorInit">C</seg>Reation, 1. GODS Image, 26. Mans ſoveraignty, 26. All very good, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 31.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 Sabbath, 3. <hi>Eden,</hi> 8. Tree of Knowledge, 17. Woman, 22. Naked and not aſhamed, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 25.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3<g ref="char:punc">▪</g> Fall, 6. Puniſhment, 16. Curſed, 17. Thruſt out of Paradiſe, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 23.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 <hi>Cain,</hi> 1. <hi>Abel,</hi> 2. <hi>Enoch,</hi> 17. <hi>Lamech,</hi> 19. <hi>Sheth,</hi> 25. <hi>Enoſh, Verſ.</hi> 26.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 5 Gencalogie to <hi>Noah,</hi> 1.29. Long lives of the Fathers, 27. <hi>Enoch</hi> taken up, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 24.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 6 Giants, 4. God repented, 6. Arke prepared, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 14.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 7 Flood, 10. 150. dayes, 24. All earthly crea<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tures dyed ſave <hi>Noah</hi> and thoſe with him, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 21.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 8 Going out of the Arke, 18. <hi>Noah</hi> ſacrificed, 20.
<pb n="2" facs="tcp:9621:4"/> All ſeaſons continue, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 22.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 9 <hi>Noah</hi> bleſſed, 1. No blood eate, 4. Rainbow, 13. <hi>Cham</hi> curſed, 25. The others bleſſed, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 26.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 10 Generation of <hi>Noahs</hi> Sonnes, 1. <hi>Iaphet,</hi> 2. <hi>Cham,</hi> 6. <hi>Shem, Verſ.</hi> 21.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 11 <hi>Babel,</hi> 9. Generations of <hi>Shem,</hi> 10. <hi>Therah</hi> his Poſterity, 27. Goes to <hi>Haran, Verſ.</hi> 31.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 12 <hi>Abram</hi> goes to <hi>Canaan,</hi> 4. Bleſſed, 3. Goes to <hi>Aegypt,</hi> 10. <hi>Pharaoh</hi> plagued, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 17.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 13 Wee be Brethren, 8. <hi>Lot</hi> to <hi>Sodome,</hi> 12. <hi>A<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>bram</hi> bleſſed, 15. Comes to <hi>Mamre, Verſ.</hi> 18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 14 Battell of Kings, 8. <hi>Lot</hi> reſcued by <hi>Abraham,</hi> 16. <hi>Melchezedech, Verſ.</hi> 18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 15 An Heire promiſed, 4. And <hi>Canaan,</hi> 7. 400. yeares, 13. Covenant with <hi>Abraham, Verſ.</hi> 18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 16 <hi>Hagar</hi> and <hi>Sarah,</hi> 3. <hi>Iſmael</hi> borne, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 15.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 17 <hi>Abraham,</hi> 1. Circumciſion, 11. <hi>Sarah,</hi> 15. <hi>I<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſaac</hi> promiſed, 19. <hi>Iſmael</hi> bleſſed, 20. Circum<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ciſed, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 23.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 18 <hi>Abraham</hi> receiveth three Angels, 5. <hi>Sarah</hi> laughed, 12. <hi>Abrahams</hi> prayer, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 23.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 19 <hi>Sodome</hi> deſtroyed, 24. <hi>Lot</hi> to <hi>Zoar,</hi> 22. <hi>Lots</hi> wife, 26. <hi>Lots</hi> inceſt, 33. <hi>Moab,</hi> 37. <hi>Ammon, Verſ.</hi> 38.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 20 <hi>Abimelech,</hi> 2. His women healed of barren<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>neſſe, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 21 <hi>Iſaac</hi> borne, 2. <hi>Hagar</hi> caſt out, 14. <hi>Abimelech,</hi> 22. <hi>Beerſheba,</hi> 31. <hi>Philiſtims, Verſ.</hi> 34.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 22 <hi>Iſaac</hi> to be offered, 10. <hi>Abraham</hi> bleſſed, 17. Generation of <hi>Nahor, Verſ.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 23 <hi>Sarah</hi> buried in <hi>Machpelah,</hi> 19. Bought of <hi>Ephron, Verſ.</hi> 20.</item>
               <pb n="3" facs="tcp:9621:4"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 24 <hi>Abrahams</hi> ſervant, 10. <hi>Rebecca</hi> conſenteth, 58. Her journey. 61. <hi>Iſaac</hi> meeteth her, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 63.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 25 <hi>Keturah,</hi> 1. <hi>Abrahams</hi> ſonnes by her, 2. His death, 8. Generation of <hi>Iſmael,</hi> 13. <hi>Eſaus</hi> birth<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>right, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 34.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 26 <hi>Iſaac</hi> at <hi>Gerar,</hi> 6. Very rich, 13. Contention, 20. Covenant with <hi>Abimelech, Verſ.</hi> 28.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 27 <hi>Iacob</hi> getteth the bleſſing, 28. <hi>Eſaus</hi> earthly bleſſing, 39. <hi>Iacob</hi> flyeth to his Vncle, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 43.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 28 <hi>Iacobs</hi> ladder, 12. Gods promiſe, 13. <hi>Bethel,</hi> 19. <hi>Iacobs</hi> vow, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 29 <hi>Rachel,</hi> 9. <hi>Leah,</hi> 25. The birth of <hi>Reuben,</hi> 32. <hi>Simeon,</hi> 33. <hi>Levi,</hi> 34. <hi>Iudah, Verſ.</hi> 35.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 30 <hi>Bilhah,</hi> 4. The birth of <hi>Dan,</hi> 6. <hi>Naphtali,</hi> 8. <hi>Zilpahs</hi> ſonnes, 11, 12. <hi>Leahs,</hi> 17. <hi>Rachels,</hi> 24. <hi>Iacobs</hi> wages, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 32.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 31 <hi>Iacob</hi> departeth, 17. <hi>Laban</hi> purſueth, 23. Con<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tention, 36. Covenant, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 44.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 32 Meſſengers to <hi>Eſau,</hi> 3. Wreſtling, 24. <hi>Iſrael,</hi> 28. <hi>Peniel,</hi> 31. Hee halteth, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 31.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 33 <hi>Iacob</hi> and <hi>Eſau</hi> meet, 4. Preſent accepted, 11. <hi>Succoth,</hi> 17. <hi>Sechem,</hi> 18. <hi>Hamor, Verſ.</hi> 19.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 34 <hi>Dinah</hi> raviſhed, 2. <hi>Sechemites</hi> ſlaine, 25. <hi>Iacob</hi> troubled, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 30.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 35 <hi>Bethel,</hi> 1. Idols buried, 4. <hi>Benjamin</hi> borne, 18. <hi>Iſaac</hi> buried, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 29.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 36 <hi>Eſaus</hi> poſterity, 1. <hi>Edomits, Verſ.</hi> 9.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 37 <hi>Ioſeph</hi> hated, 4. Dreameth, 6. Sold to the <hi>Iſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>maelites,</hi> 28. By them to <hi>Potiphar, Verſ.</hi> 36.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 38 <hi>Iudah,</hi> 2. <hi>Er,</hi> 7. <hi>Onan,</hi> 9. <hi>Thamar</hi> with child by <hi>Iudah,</hi> 24. <hi>Pharez</hi> and <hi>Zarah, Verſ.</hi> 29.</item>
               <pb n="4" facs="tcp:9621:5"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 39 <hi>Ioſephs</hi> Miſtres, 7. Accuſeth him. 17. Hee fin<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>deth favour in Priſon, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 21.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 40 <hi>Pharoahs</hi> Butler and Baker impriſoned, 3. Their dreames interpreted, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 12.18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 41 <hi>Pharoahs</hi> two, Dreames, 25. <hi>Ioſeph</hi> ſtores up Corne, 49. The famine begins, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 54.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 42 <hi>Iacobs</hi> tenne Sonnes bow before <hi>Ioſeph,</hi> 6. <hi>Si<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>meon</hi> kept, 24. <hi>Ioſeph</hi> wept, <hi>ibid.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 43 <hi>Benjamin</hi> ſent, 13. <hi>Ioſeph</hi> entertaines them at his houſe, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 24.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 44 Cup in <hi>Benjamins</hi> ſacke, 12. <hi>Iudahs</hi> ſupplica<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tion, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 45 <hi>Ioſeph</hi> made knowne to his Brethren, 3. <hi>Iacob</hi> is ſent for, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 9.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 46 70. Soules come to <hi>Egypt,</hi> 27. They are pla<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ced in <hi>Goſhen, Verſ.</hi> 28.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 47 <hi>Iacob</hi> comes before <hi>Pharoah,</hi> 7. The <hi>Egypti<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ans</hi> ſell all for Corne, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 15.18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 48 <hi>Ephraim</hi> ſet before <hi>Manaſſeh, Verſ.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 49 <hi>Iacob</hi> bleſſeth his Sonnes, 28. Chargeth for his buriall, 29. Dyeth, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 33.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 50 Great mourning at <hi>Iacobs</hi> funerall, 10. <hi>Ioſeph</hi> comforteth his Brethren, 21. Giveth charge of his bones, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 25.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>EXODVS.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ch<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>.</hi> 1 <hi>ISrael</hi> oppreſſed, 11. Multiply, 12. Midwives rewarded by God, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 21.</item>
               <pb n="5" facs="tcp:9621:5"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ch<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>.</hi> 2 <hi>Moſes</hi> taken out of the water, 5. Fled to <hi>Mi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dian,</hi> 15. God heard <hi>Iſraels</hi> groaning, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 24.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ch<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>.</hi> 3 Buſh, 2. God promiſeth to deliver <hi>Iſrael,</hi> 10. Sends <hi>Moſes</hi> to tell <hi>Iſrael</hi> thereof, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 16.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ch<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>.</hi> 4 Rod a Serpent, 3. Hand leprous, 6. Blood, 9. <hi>Aaron,</hi> 14. <hi>Zipporah,</hi> 25. <hi>Iſrael</hi> beleeved, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 31.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ch<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>.</hi> 5 <hi>Pharoah</hi> increaſed their burdens, 7. Officers bea<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ten, 14. Complaint to <hi>Moſes,</hi> 20. He to God, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 22.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ch<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>.</hi> 6 <hi>Jehovah,</hi> 3. Deliuerance promiſed, 6. <hi>Iſrael</hi> hearkened not, 9. Generations, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 14.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ch<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>.</hi> 7 Rods into Serpents, 12. Waters blood, 20. So did Enchanters, 21. <hi>Pharoah</hi> hardened, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 22.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ch<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>.</hi> 8 Frogs, 6. <hi>Pharoah</hi> ſues to <hi>Moſes,</hi> 8. Lice, 17. Sorcerers could not, 18. Flies, 24. <hi>Pharoah</hi> hard<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ned, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 32.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ch<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>.</hi> 9 Murraine, 6. Blaines, 10. Haile, 23. <hi>Pharoah</hi> con<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>feſſeth his ſinne, 27. Yet hardened, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 34.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ch<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>.</hi> 10 Locuſts, 4. <hi>Pharoahs</hi> ſervants intreat, 7. Hum<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>bled, 16. Hardned, 20. Darknes, 22. See not, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 23.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ch<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>.</hi> 11 Laſt plague threatned, <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>. People in favour with the <hi>Egyptians,</hi> 3. <hi>Pharoah</hi> hardned, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 10.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ch<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>.</hi> 12 Paſſeover, 3. Firſt <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                     <desc>••</desc>
                  </gap>rne ſlaine, 29. Borrowed jewels, 35. Come to <hi>Succoth, Verſe.</hi> 37.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ch<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>.</hi> 13 Firſt borne, 2. Feaſt in memoriall thereof, 6. <hi>Ioſephs</hi> bones, 19. Cloud, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 22.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ch<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>.</hi> 14 <hi>Pharoah</hi> purſueth, 5. People murmure, 11. <hi>Pharoah</hi> drowned, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 28.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ch<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>.</hi> 15 Songs, 1. <hi>Marah,</hi> 23. Murmure, 24. Promiſe to obedience, 26. Twelue Wells at <hi>Elim, Verſe.</hi> 27.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ch<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>.</hi> 16 Wildernes of Sin, 1. Murmure, 2. Quailes, 13. Manna, 15. Reſerved, 20. Sabbath, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 23.</item>
               <pb n="6" facs="tcp:9621:6"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ch<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>.</hi> 17 Murmure, 2. <hi>Meribah,</hi> 7. <hi>Amalek</hi> overcome, 13. Curſed, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 16.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ch<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>.</hi> 18 <hi>Iethro</hi> comes to <hi>Moſes,</hi> 5. His counſell, 19. Rulers choſen, 25. <hi>Iethro</hi> departeth, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 27.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ch<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>.</hi> 19 <hi>Sinai,</hi> 1. Promiſes, 5. Great preparation for the Law, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 10.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ch<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>.</hi> 20 Ten Commandements, 1. Tremble, 18. No I<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dols, 23. Altar how to be made, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 24.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ch<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>.</hi> 21 Lawes for Servants, <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>. Murther. 12. Man ſtea<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ling, 16. Curſe Parents, 17. Smiting, 20. Oxe, 28. Pit, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 33.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ch<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>.</hi> 22 Theft, 1. Betrothed, 16. Witch, 18. Stranger, 21. Widow, 22. Lending, 25. Firſt fruits, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 29.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ch<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>.</hi> 23 Iuſtice, 6. Stranger, 9. Seventh yeere, 11. Sab<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>bath, 12. Feaſts, 14. Gods Angell, 23. Hor<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nets, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 28.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ch<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>.</hi> 24 Seventy Elders, 1. Booke of the Covenant, 7. Forty dayes in the Mount, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ch<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>.</hi> 25 Offerings for Tabernacle, 2. Arke, 10. Mercy Seat, 17. Table, <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                     <desc>••</desc>
                  </gap>. Candleſtick, 31. Inſtru<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ments thereof, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 38.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ch<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>.</hi> 26 Forme of Tabernacle Curtaines, 2. Cove<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rings, 7. Boards, 15. Vaile, 31. Doore, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 36.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ch<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>.</hi> 27 Altar, 1. Veſſels, 3. Court, 9. Oyle, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ch<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>.</hi> 28 <hi>Aaron</hi> and his Sonnes garments, 2. Ephod, 6. Breſt-plate, 15. Miter, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 36.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ch<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>.</hi> 29 Conſecration, 1. Daily ſacrifice, 38. God will dwell with <hi>Iſrael, Verſe.</hi> 45.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ch<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>.</hi> 30 Incence Altar, 1. Ranſome, 12. Laver, 18. Ho<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ly Oyle, 23. Perfume, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 34.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ch<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>.</hi> 31 <hi>Bezaleel,</hi> 2. Sabbath a figne, 17. Two Tables, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 18</item>
               <pb n="7" facs="tcp:9621:6"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ch<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>.</hi> 32 Calfe, 4. <hi>Moſes</hi> appeaſeth God, 11. Ta<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>bles broke, 19. Three thouſand ſlaine, 28. Blot me, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 33.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ch<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>.</hi> 33 Angell, 2. Put off ornaments, 5. Face to face, 11. Gods back parts, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 23.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ch<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>.</hi> 34 New Tables, 1: Gods glory, 5. No Covenant, 12. Sundry lawes, 13. Forty dayes, 28. Shi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ned, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 29.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ch<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>.</hi> 35 No fire, 3<g ref="char:punc">▪</g> Free gifts, 5. <hi>Bezaleel</hi> and <hi>Aholiah</hi> filled with the Spirit, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 30.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ch<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>.</hi> 36 Too much, 5. Making of the Tabernacle, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 8.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ch<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>.</hi> 37 Arke, 1. Mercy ſeat, 6. Table, 10. Veſſels, 16. Candleſtick, 17. Oyle, 29. Incence, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 29.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ch<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>.</hi> 38 Altar, 1. Laver, 8. Court, 9. Hangings, 11. The ſumme of Gold, 24. Silver, 25. Braſſe, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 29.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ch<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>.</hi> 39 Ephod, 2. Breſt-plate, 8. Robe with bells, 25. Coates, 27. Miter, 28. Crowne, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 30.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ch<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                        <desc>••</desc>
                     </gap>.</hi> 40 All reared, 2. <hi>Aaron</hi> and his ſonnes Sanctified, 13. Cloud filled, 34. Removed, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 36.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>LEVITICVS.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 BVrnt Offerings of herds, 2. Flockes, 10. Fowles, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 14.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 Meat offerings, 1. Firſt fruits, 12. Salt of the Covenant not wanting, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 13.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 Peace offerings of herd, 1. Flocks, 6. Lambe, 7. Goat, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 12.</item>
               <pb n="8" facs="tcp:9621:7"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 Sinne offerings of ignorance, 2. For Prieſt, 3. Congregation, 13. Ruler, 22. People, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 27.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 5 Offerings for ſinnes knowne, 1. Treſpaſſe in holy things knowne or unknowne, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 15.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 6 For ſinne done wittingly, 2. Law of burnt Of<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ferings, 9. Conſecration, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 7 Law of treſpaſſe offerings. 1. All the Prieſts, 9. Thankeſgiving, 12. Fat and blood not ea<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ten, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 23.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 8 Conſecration of <hi>Aaron</hi> and his Sonnes, 6. The offerings thereat, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 14.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 9 <hi>Aaron</hi> offereth for himſelfe, 8. And the peo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ple, 15. Bleſſed, 22. Fire from God, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 24.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 10 <hi>Nadab,</hi> 1. No wine, 9. Prieſts eate in holy place 12. <hi>Aarons</hi> excuſe, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 19.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 11 Cleane and uncleane Beaſts, 3. Fiſhes, 9. Fowles 13. Creeping things, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 29.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 12 Women purified, 2. Their offerings, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 8.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 13 Marks of Leproſie on men, 2. Or garments, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 47.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 14 Offerings for cleanſing of Lepers, 2. Leproſie in an houſe, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 34.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 15 Iſſues of Men and Women, 2. Clenſed, 13. 19. Their offerings, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 14.28.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 16 Entering in to the Holy place, 2. Offerings, 11. Scape-goate, 21. Day of attonement, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 29.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 17 No blood eaten, 10. Nor which dyeth alone, 15. Or is torne, <hi>ibid.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 18 Vnlawfull marriages, 6. Other filthy abhomi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nations, 19. Land ſinne, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 25.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 19 Repetition of ſundry Lawes, 3. Gleaning, 9. No mingling, 19. Mercy, 33. Iuſtice, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 36.</item>
               <pb n="9" facs="tcp:9621:7"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 20 <hi>Molech,</hi> 2. Wizards, 6. Inceſt, 19. Buggery 15. Cleane beaſts, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 25.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 21 Prieſts holineſſe, 6. Not to mourne, 11. No blemiſh, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 17.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 22 No Prieſt uncleane may eate Holy things, 2. What ſacrifices eaten, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 19.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 23 Feaſts of Sabbath, 3. Paſſeover, 5. Firſt fruits, 10. Pentecoſt. 15. Trumpets, 23. Taberna<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cles, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 33.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 24 Oyle, 2. Shew-bread, 5. Blaſphemer dye, 11. Murther 17. Damage, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 25 Seventh yeare, 2. Sabbath, 4. Iubile, 8. Sale of land, 14. Poore, 25. Bondmen redeemed, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 44.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 26 No Idolater, 1. Bleſſing to obedience, 3. Cur<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſes to diſobedience, 14. Mercy to humble, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 40.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 27 Perſons vowed, 2. Beaſts, 9. Houſes redee<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>med, 15. Devoted, 28. Tythe, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 30.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>NVMBERS.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 ELeven Tribes numbred, 5. Levites not num<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>bred, 47. Pitch about the Tabernacle, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 50.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 The order of the Tribes in their rents. <hi>Through<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>out the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 Levites taken for the firſt borne, 12. Their number and order, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 17.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 Services of the three Families of the Levites. <hi>Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <pb n="10" facs="tcp:9621:8"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 5 Vncleane out of the Campe, 2. Reſtitution, 6. Iealouſie, 12. Bitter water, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 6 Law of <hi>Nazarites,</hi> 2. Prieſts bleſſe the peo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ple, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 23.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 7 Severall offerings of the Princes, 2. God ſpake to <hi>Moſes, <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 89.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 8 Lamps, 2. Levites conſecrated, 6. Their time of their ſervice, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 24.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 9 Paſſeover, 2. Vncleane in the ſecond moneth, 6. Cloud guides their journeyes, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 10 Trumpets, 2. Remove to <hi>Paran,</hi> 12. Order of march, 14. <hi>Moſes</hi> bleſſing, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 35.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 11 <hi>Taberah,</hi> 3. Luſting, 4. 70 Elders, 16. <hi>Eldad,</hi> 26. Quailes, 31. Great Plague, 33. <hi>Kibroth, <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 34.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 12 <hi>Miriams</hi> leproſie, 10. Shut out of the Hoaſt, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 15.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 13 Twelue Spyes, 3. Their report, 26. <hi>Caleb</hi> ſtil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>leth the people, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 30.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 14 Murmure, 2. <hi>Ioſhua</hi> and <hi>Caleb,</hi> 6. <hi>Moſes</hi> pray<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>er, 13. Forty yeares, 33. <hi>Amalek, <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 43.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 15 Divers Sacrifices, 3. Preſumptuous dye, 30. Ga<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>thered ſtickes ſtoned, 32. Fringes, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 38.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 16 <hi>Korah,</hi> 1. Earth ſwallowed, 31. 250 burnt, 35. 14000 and 700 ſlaine, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 49.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 17 <hi>Aarons</hi> rod buddeth, 8. Its kept, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 10.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 18 Prieſts and Levites charges, 1. And portions, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 9.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 19 Water of Purification, 12. The uncleane not purified cut off, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 20 <hi>Miriam</hi> dyeth, 1. Rock ſmitten, 11. <hi>Edom</hi> de<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nyeth paſſage, 18. <hi>Aaron</hi> dyeth, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 28.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 21 <hi>Hermah,</hi> 3. Fiery Serpents, 6. Iournies, 10.
<pb n="11" facs="tcp:9621:8"/> 
                  <hi>Sihon,</hi> 21. <hi>Og</hi> deſtroyed, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 33.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 22 <hi>Balaam</hi> refuſeth, 13, His Aſſe, 23. Hee comes to <hi>Balak, <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 36.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 23 <hi>Balaams</hi> ſacrifices, 2. His Parables, 7. Bleſſing <hi>Iſrael, <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 19.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 24 <hi>Balaam</hi> ſtill bleſſeth <hi>Iſrael,</hi> 5. Prophecies a<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gainſt <hi>Edom,</hi> 18. <hi>Amalek, <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 25 Whoredome with <hi>Moab,</hi> 1. <hi>Phineas,</hi> 7. Vexe the <hi>Midianites, <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 17.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 26 Summe of all <hi>Iſrael</hi> 601730, 51. Levites 23000, 62. Not of the former number, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 64.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 27 Daughters of <hi>Zelophead,</hi> 1. <hi>Moſes</hi> ſees <hi>Cana<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>an,</hi> 12. <hi>Joſhua</hi> ſucceeds, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 23.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 28 Daily Offerings, 2. Double on Sabbath, 9. New Moones, 11. Paſſeover, 16. Firſt fruits, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 26.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 29 Offrings at day of Trumpets, 1. And of recon<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ciliation, 7. Tabernacles, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 13.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 30 Vowes of Maids, 3. Wives, 6. Widowes, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 9.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 31 <hi>Midianites</hi> and <hi>Balaam</hi> ſlaine, 8. Women ſa<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ved ſlaine, 17. Lords portion, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 48.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 32 <hi>Reubenites, Gadites,</hi> and halfe tribe of <hi>Manaſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſes,</hi> have the land of the <hi>Amorites. Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 33 Forty two journies, 1. <hi>Cananites</hi> if not deſtroy<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ed, 52. Left as prickes, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 55.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 34 Borders of the Land, 2. Names of them that divide the Land, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 17.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 35 Forty eight Cities for Levites, 2. Sixe for re<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>fuge, 6. Lawes for Murther, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 11.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 36 Inheritance muſt not paſſe from Tribe to tribe. <hi>Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <pb n="12" facs="tcp:9621:9"/>
               <head>DEVTERONOMIE.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 REhearſall of divers things, 4. Officers, 15: Spyes, 19. Gods anger for murmuring, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 34.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 Iournies, 1. Not to meddle with <hi>Edom</hi> and <hi>Moab,</hi> 4. <hi>Amorites</hi> deſtroyed, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 24.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 <hi>Og</hi> deſtroyed, 1. His bed, 11. Two Tribes and halfe, 12. <hi>Moſes</hi> ſhould ſee <hi>Canaan, <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 27.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 Exhortation to Obedience, 1. With threats, 23. Cities for refuge, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 41.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 5 Tenne Commandements, 6. People crave <hi>Mo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſes</hi> to ſpeake to them, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 24.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 6 Teach Children, 7. Forget not, 12. Our righ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>teouſneſſe, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 25.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 7 Seven Nations, 1. God loved thee, 7. Bleſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſings, 12. Hornet, 20. No Image, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 25.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 8 Fed thee with Manna, 3. Forget not, 11. Yee ſhall periſh, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 19.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 9 Not for thy righteouſneſſe, 5. Their continuall rebellions, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 7.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 10 Reſtoring two Tables, 2. Levites ſeparated, 8. Exhortation to obedience, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 12.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 11 Gods mighty workes, 2. Laud God, 12. Bleſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſings and Curſes, 22. <hi>Gerizim</hi> and <hi>Eball, <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 29.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 12 Idolatry deſtroyed, 2. Place for Worſhip, 5. No blood, 23. Not to adde or diminiſh, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 32.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 13 Inticers to Idolatry ſtoned, 10. And ſuch Cities deſtroyed, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 12.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 14 Cleane and uncleane, 4. Tithes, 23. Third yeres
<pb n="13" facs="tcp:9621:9"/> tythe for the Levites and Strangers, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 28.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 15 Seventh yeere free, 1. Poore, 4. Hebrew ſer<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>vant, 12. Firſt things ſanctified, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 19.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 16 Paſſeover, 1. Pentecoſt, 9. Tabernacles, 13. Iud<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ges, 18. No Groves, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 21.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 17 Idolaters ſlaine, 2. Prieſt Iudge, 9. Contemners dye, 12. Duty of King, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 16.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 18 Levits portion God, 2. Not as Nations, 9. Pro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>phet good or bad knowne, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 21.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 19 Refuge for Man-ſleyer, 2. Land markes, 14. Two witneſſes, 15. Falſe witneſſe, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 16.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 20 Diſmiſſed from Warre, 5. What Cities ſpared or deſtroyed, 10. Fruit trees, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 19.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 21 Found ſlaine, 1. Captive wife, 10. Firſt borne 15. Rebellious Sonne, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 22 Stray, 1. Sexe, 5. No mixture, 9. Divorce, 13. Betrothed, 23. Rape, 28. Inceſt, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 30.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 23 Enter the Congregation, 1. Vncleanneſſe, 9. No Whore, 17. Vſury, 19. Vowes, 21. Treſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>paſſes, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 24.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 24 Divorce, 1. Pledge, 10. Man ſtealer, 7. Lend Poore, 10. Hire, 14. Iuſtice, 16. Gleaning, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 19.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 25 Forty ſtripes, 3. Oxe, 4. Raiſe ſeed, 5. Hands cut off, 12. Weights, 14. <hi>Amalek, <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 17.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 26 Confeſſing at Offerings the firſt fruites, 5. And tythes, 12. God thine, thou Gods, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 16.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 27 Law writ on ſtones, 2. Six Tribes to bleſſe, and ſixe to curſe, 12. Who curſed, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 15.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 28 Bleſſings, 3. And curſes, 16. Eate Children, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 53.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 29 Former workes of God, 2. Covenant with all <hi>Iſrael,</hi> 10. Preſumption, 18. Secret to God, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 20.</item>
               <pb n="14" facs="tcp:9621:10"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 30 Mercy to Penitent, 3. Word neere thee, 14. Life and death, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 15.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 31 <hi>Moſes</hi> encourageth the people, 3. And <hi>Ioſhua,</hi> 7. Law read on the Seventh yeere, 11. Reade this Song, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 30.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 32 Song, 1. Gods mercies, 7. And vengeance, 19. <hi>Nebo, <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 49.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 33 Bleſſing of the twelue Tribes, 2. Who is like Iſrael, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 29.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 34 <hi>Moſes</hi> ſeeth <hi>Canaan,</hi> 1. Dyeth, 5. Thirty dayes Mourning, 8. None like <hi>Moſes, <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 10.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>IOSHVA.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 GOD will be with <hi>Ioſhua,</hi> 5. <hi>Reubenites, Ga<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dites, &amp;c.</hi> promiſe <hi>Ioſhua</hi> fealty, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 16.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 <hi>Rahab</hi> ſaveth the Spyes, 6. Takes oath for her and hers, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 12.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 People Sanctified to paſſe over <hi>Iordan.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap> Twelue Stones, 5. God magnifieth <hi>Ioſhua,</hi> 14 <hi>Gilgal, <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 5 Circumciſion, 8. Paſſeover, 10. Manna ceaſed, 12. Angell appeared to <hi>Ioſhua, <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 13.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 6 <hi>Iericho</hi> accurſed, 18. Walls fall, 20. All de<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtroyed ſave <hi>Rahabs</hi> kindred, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 21.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 7 <hi>Iſrael</hi> diſcomfited at <hi>Ai,</hi> 5. Faſted, 6. <hi>Achan</hi> and all his Stoned, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 25.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 8 <hi>Ai</hi> taken, 19. King hanged, 29. Altar, 31. Law
<pb n="15" facs="tcp:9621:10"/> written, 32. Stones, 33. Bleſſings, 34. Curſes, <hi>ibid.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 9 Kings joyne, 1. <hi>Gibeonites</hi> make league, 15. They be curſed, 23. Bondmen, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 27.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 10 Five Kings diſcomfited, 10. Haileſtones, 11. Sun ſtood a Day, 13. Seven Kings overcome, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 28.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 11 Many Kings overcome, 8. <hi>Hazor</hi> taken, 10. The <hi>Anakims</hi> cut off, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 22.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 12 The Kings whom <hi>Ioſhua</hi> overcame on both ſides of <hi>Jordan.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 13 Land not yet conquered, 1. The Inheritance of the two Tribes and halfe, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 15.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 14 9. Tribes inherit by lot, 1. <hi>Caleb</hi> hath <hi>Hebron, <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 13</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 15 <hi>Iudah</hi> his lot, 1. <hi>Calebs</hi> portion, 13. <hi>Othniel,</hi> 17 Cities of <hi>Iudah, <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 21.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 16 <hi>Ioſephs</hi> lot, 1. <hi>Ephraims,</hi> 5. <hi>Cananites</hi> not con<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>quered, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 10.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 17 <hi>Manaſſes</hi> lot, 1. Another lot for <hi>Ioſephs</hi> Chil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dren, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 14.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 18 Tabernacle ſet up at <hi>Shiloh,</hi> 1. Land into ſeven parts, 2. <hi>Benjamins</hi> lot, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 11.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 19 Lots of <hi>Simeon,</hi> 1. <hi>Zebulon,</hi> 10. <hi>Iſſachar,</hi> 17. <hi>Aſher,</hi> 24. <hi>Nephtali,</hi> 32. <hi>Dan,</hi> 40. <hi>Ioſhua, <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 49.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 20 Sixe Cities of Refuge ſet out.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 21 Forty eight Cities for the Levites, 41. Land had reſt, 44. Nothing failed, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 45.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 22 Two Tribes and halfe ſent home, 6. Altar of witneſſe, 10. People appeaſed, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 33.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 23 <hi>Ioſhua</hi> encourageth Iſrael, 2. Promiſes, 10. Threats, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 13.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>4 Rehearſall of Gods benefits, 2. Covenant, 25. Stone a witneſſe, 27. <hi>Ioſephs</hi> bones buried, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 32.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <pb n="16" facs="tcp:9621:11"/>
               <head>IVDGES.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 ADONIBEZEK, 5. <hi>Ieruſalem,</hi> 8. <hi>Othniel,</hi> 13. Many <hi>Cananites</hi> not driven out, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 27.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 <hi>B<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>chim,</hi> 1. Served <hi>Baalim,</hi> 11. Gods anger, 14 And p<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>rty, <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>6. <hi>Cananites</hi> left, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 23.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 Nations left <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 word">
                     <desc>〈◊〉</desc>
                  </gap> prove <hi>Iſrael,</hi> 1. <hi>Othniel,</hi> 9. <hi>E<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>hud,</hi> 
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>5. <hi>Shamgar, <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 31.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 <hi>Deborah,</hi> 4. <hi>Barak,</hi> 6. <hi>Siſera,</hi> 13. Slaine by <hi>Iael, <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 21.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 5 Song of <hi>Deborah. Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 6 <hi>Godeon,</hi> 11. Deſtroyes <hi>Baals</hi> Altar, 25. <hi>Ierub<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>baal,</hi> 32. His Signes, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 37.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 7 <hi>Gedeon</hi> with 300 overcomes the <hi>Midiaenites,</hi> 22. <hi>Oreb</hi> and <hi>Zeeb, <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 25.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 8 <hi>Succoth,</hi> 5. <hi>Penuel,</hi> 8. <hi>Zeba</hi> and <hi>Zalmunnah,</hi> 10. <hi>Ephod,</hi> 27. <hi>Baal-Berith, <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 33.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 9 <hi>Abimelech</hi> King, 6. <hi>Iothams</hi> Parable, 8. <hi>Gaal,</hi> 26. <hi>Zebul,</hi> 30. <hi>Abimelech</hi> ſlaine, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 53.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 10 <hi>Tola,</hi> 1. <hi>Iair,</hi> 3. <hi>Philiſtims</hi> oppreſſe them, 7. God reproves, 11. And pitties them, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 16.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 11 <hi>Iephtah</hi> overcomes <hi>Ammon,</hi> 33. Performeth his vow on his Daughter, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 39.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 12 <hi>Ephramites</hi> ſlaine, 6. <hi>Ibzan,</hi> 8. <hi>Elon,</hi> 11. <hi>Ab<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>den,</hi> 13. Iudges.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 13 <hi>M<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>noah,</hi> 2. <hi>Samſon</hi> is borne, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 24.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 14 <hi>Samſons</hi> riddle, 14. Kils 30 <hi>Philiſtinis,</hi> 19. His wife given to another, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 20.</item>
               <pb n="17" facs="tcp:9621:11"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 15 300 Foxes, 4. Burnes <hi>Philiſtims</hi> corne, 5. Smote them, 8. Is bound, 13. Sleyeth 1000, 15. <hi>Le<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>hi, <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 19.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 16 Hee carried the Gates, 3. <hi>Dalilah,</hi> 4. <hi>Samſons</hi> eyes put out, 21. Death, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 30.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 17 <hi>Micah,</hi> 1. No King, 6. Levite was his Prieſt, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 7.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 18 <hi>Danites</hi> take away <hi>Micahs</hi> Prieſt, 19. Take and burne <hi>Laiſh,</hi> 27. Build <hi>Dan. <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 29.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 19 Levits Concubine at <hi>Gibeah</hi> abuſed, 28. Cut in twelve peeces and ſent to the 12 Tribes, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 29.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 20 <hi>Benjamites</hi> twice vanquiſh, 21. Are vanquiſh<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ed. 35. Cities burnt, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 48.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 21 <hi>Iabeſh Gilead</hi> (ſave 400 Virgins) deſtroyed, 12. Daughters of <hi>Shiloh, <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 19.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>RVTH.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 <hi>NAomy's</hi> husband, 3. And Sonnes dyed, 5. <hi>Orpah</hi> returneth, 14. <hi>Ruth</hi> abides, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 16.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 <hi>Ruth</hi> gleanes, 7. <hi>Boaz</hi> kindneſſe, 8. <hi>Ruth</hi> cari<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ed home ſtore, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 <hi>Ruth</hi> lyeth at <hi>Boaz</hi> feet, 7. Hee yeelds to her deſire, 13. And relieves her, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 15.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 <hi>Boaz</hi> his kinſman refuſing. 6. He marries <hi>Ruth,</hi> 13. <hi>Obed,</hi> 17. <hi>Ieſſe-David, <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 22.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <pb n="18" facs="tcp:9621:12"/>
               <head>1. SAMVEL.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 <hi>HAnnah</hi> beareth <hi>Samuel,</hi> 20. Preſents him to the Lord, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 28.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 <hi>Hannahs</hi> Song, 1. <hi>Elyes</hi> Sonnes wicked, 22. Heavie threatnings againſt him, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 31.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 <hi>Samuel</hi> called, 4. Heavie tidings to <hi>Ely,</hi> 12. God appeared to <hi>Samuel, Verſ.</hi> 21.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 <hi>Philiſtims</hi> overcome Iſrael, 10. Arke taken, 11. <hi>Ely</hi> breakes his necke, 18. <hi>Icabod, Verſ.</hi> 21.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 5 <hi>Dagon</hi> falls before the Arke, 4. Men of <hi>Aſh<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dod,</hi> 6. <hi>Gath,</hi> 8. <hi>Ekron,</hi> 10. Emorods, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 12.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 6 Arke ſent backe, 11. Men of <hi>Beth-Shemeſh</hi> ſlaine, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 19.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 7 Arke in <hi>Kiriath Iearim</hi> twenty yeares, 2. <hi>E<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ben-Ezer,</hi> 12. <hi>Philiſtims</hi> ſubdued, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 13.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 8 <hi>Iſrael</hi> aske a King, 5. <hi>Samuel</hi> told the oppreſſi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>on of the King <hi>Verſ.</hi> 11.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 9 <hi>Saul</hi> commeth to <hi>Samuel</hi> about his fathers Aſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſes. <hi>Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 10 <hi>Saul</hi> anointed, 1. Is confirmed, 9. He Prophe<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cieth, 10. Choſen at <hi>Miſpeh, Verſ.</hi> 24.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 11 <hi>Iabeſh Gilead,</hi> 1. <hi>Ammonites</hi> ſlaine, 11. <hi>Saul</hi> made King in <hi>Gilgal, Verſ.</hi> 15.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 12 <hi>Samuel</hi> rehearſeth his Integrity, 3. Gods mer<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cies, 8. Thunder, 18. Exhortation to repent, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 13 <hi>Philiſtims</hi> great Hoaſt, 5. <hi>Saul</hi> ſacrificeth, 9. Reproved, 13. No Smith in <hi>Iſrael, Verſ.</hi> 19.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 14 <hi>Ionathan</hi> and his Armour-bearer, 6. <hi>Philiſtims</hi>
                  <pb n="19" facs="tcp:9621:12"/> flie, 15. <hi>Sauls</hi> adjuration, 24. Honey, 27. Eat with blood, 32. <hi>Jonathan</hi> ſaved, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 45.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 15 <hi>Saul</hi> ſpareth <hi>Agag,</hi> 9. His Sin and judgement, 26. <hi>Agag</hi> ſlaine, 33. <hi>Samuel</hi> mournes, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 35.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 16 <hi>David</hi> ſecretly anointed, 13. <hi>Saul</hi> ſends for him to quiet his Spirit, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 19.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 17 <hi>David</hi> kils <hi>Goliah,</hi> 50. <hi>Saul</hi> takes notice o<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap> him, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 55.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 18 <hi>David</hi> and <hi>Ionathans</hi> Covenant, 3. <hi>Sauls</hi> en<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>vie, 9. <hi>Michall,</hi> 20. 200 Fore-skins, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 27.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 19 <hi>Saul</hi> reconciled, 7. Yet ſought his life, 10. <hi>Mi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>chol</hi> ſaves him, 12. <hi>Naieth, Verſ.</hi> 18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 20 <hi>David</hi> and <hi>Ionathan</hi> renue Covenant, 16. Three arrowes, 20. <hi>Ionathan</hi> reviled, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 30.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 21 <hi>David</hi> eates of the Shew-bread, 6. Faineth himſelfe mad, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 13.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 22 Many reſort to <hi>David,</hi> 2. His Parents at <hi>Mo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ab,</hi> 4. <hi>Doeg</hi> kils the Lords Prieſts, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 23 <hi>Keilah,</hi> 1. <hi>Ziph.</hi> 14. <hi>Ionathan,</hi> 16. <hi>Ziphits,</hi> 15. <hi>Maon,</hi> 24. <hi>Philiſtims</hi> invade, 27. <hi>Enge<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>di, Verſ.</hi> 29.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 24 <hi>Sauls</hi> skirt, 4. <hi>Davids</hi> innocency, 15. <hi>Sauls</hi> Confeſſion, 17. <hi>Davids</hi> oath, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 22.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 25 <hi>Samuel</hi> dyeth, 1. <hi>Nabal,</hi> 10. <hi>Abigal,</hi> 18. <hi>Da<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>vid</hi> taketh her to wife, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 42.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 26 <hi>David</hi> ſpareth <hi>Saul,</hi> 11. <hi>Abner</hi> reproved, 16, Speakes to <hi>Saul,</hi> 18. Who confeſſeth, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 21.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 27 <hi>David</hi> goes to <hi>Gath,</hi> 2. <hi>Ziglag,</hi> 6. Deſtroyes the <hi>Geſhurites,</hi> 8. Tels untruth, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 10.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 28 <hi>Saul</hi> goes to a Witch, 8. Heares heavie tidings, 19. Faints, 20. Is comforted, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 23.</item>
               <pb n="20" facs="tcp:9621:13"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 29 <hi>David</hi> is ſent backe from warre by <hi>Achis,</hi> 7. Who commends him, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 9.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 30 <hi>Ziglag</hi> burnt, 1. <hi>Amaleks</hi> ſurpriſed, 16. Spoile divided, 24. Sends preſents, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 26.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 31 <hi>Iſrael</hi> overcome, 1. <hi>Sauls</hi> death, 4. Men of <hi>Ia<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>beſh</hi> tooke the bodies, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 11.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>2. SAMVEL:</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 AN <hi>Amalekite</hi> ſaying hee ſlew <hi>Saul</hi> is ſlaine, 15. <hi>David</hi> laments for <hi>Saul, Verſ.</hi> 17.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 <hi>David</hi> King of <hi>Judah,</hi> 4. <hi>Iſhboſheth</hi> of <hi>Iſrael,</hi> 8. Warre, 17. <hi>Aſahel</hi> ſlaine, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 23.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 Long warre, 1. <hi>Abners</hi> league, 13. <hi>Ioah</hi> killeth him, 27. Is curſed, 29. <hi>David</hi> mourneth, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 31.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 <hi>Iſhboſheth</hi> killed, 7. The murtherers executed, 12. His head buried, <hi>ibid.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 5 All <hi>Iſrael</hi> makes <hi>David</hi> King, 3. <hi>Zion</hi> taken, 9. <hi>Hiram,</hi> 11. <hi>Philiſtims</hi> overcome, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 25.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 6 Arke removed, 3. <hi>Vzzah,</hi> 7. <hi>Obediah</hi> bleſſed, 12. Arke to <hi>Sion, ibid. Michol</hi> ſcoffeth. 16. Bar<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ren, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 23.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 7 <hi>David</hi> would but ſhould not build Gods houſe, 5. Gods Promiſe, 13. <hi>Davids</hi> thankes, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 8 <hi>Davids</hi> Victories, 1. He dedicated, 11. Garri<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſons in <hi>Edom,</hi> 14. Officers, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 16.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 9 <hi>Mephiboſheth</hi> advanced, 7. <hi>Ziba, Verſ.</hi> 9.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 10 <hi>Hanun</hi> abuſeth <hi>Davids</hi> ſervants, 4, <hi>Ammo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nites</hi>
                  <pb n="21" facs="tcp:9621:13"/> and <hi>Syrians</hi> overcome, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 14.18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 11 <hi>Davids</hi> adultery with <hi>Bathſheba,</hi> 4. <hi>Vriah</hi> ſlaine 17. <hi>David</hi> takes <hi>Bathſheba, Verſ.</hi> 27.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 12 <hi>Nathan</hi> reproves <hi>David,</hi> 7. Who mournes for the Child, 16. <hi>Solomon,</hi> 24. <hi>Rabbah, Verſ.</hi> 29.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 13 <hi>Amnon</hi> defloures <hi>Thamar,</hi> 14. Is ſlaine by <hi>Ab<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſolam,</hi> 29. Who flyeth, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 37.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 14 <hi>Abſolam</hi> is brought backe, 23. After two yeares ſees the King, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 33.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 15 <hi>Abſolams</hi> conſpiracy, 6. <hi>David</hi> flyeth, 14. Arke, 25. <hi>Huſhai</hi> returned, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 37.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 16 <hi>Ziba,</hi> 1. <hi>Shemei,</hi> 5. <hi>Huſhai</hi> comes to <hi>Abſo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lam,</hi> 16. <hi>Achitophels</hi> counſell, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 23.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 17 <hi>Achitophels</hi> councell rejected, 14. His death, 23 Two meſſengers, 17. <hi>David</hi> relieved, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 27.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 18 <hi>Abſolam</hi> overthrowne, 15. <hi>David</hi> mourneth for him, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 33.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 19 <hi>Joah</hi> moves <hi>David</hi> to ceaſe mourning, 8. <hi>Iu<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dah,</hi> 11. <hi>Shemei,</hi> 18. <hi>Mephiboſh.</hi> 24. <hi>Barzillai, Verſ.</hi> 31.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 20 <hi>Sheba,</hi> 1. <hi>Amaſa</hi> ſlaine by <hi>Ioab,</hi> 9. <hi>Abel</hi> beſie<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ged, 15. <hi>Sheba</hi> beheaded, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 22.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 21 Three yeares Famine, 1. Seven of <hi>Sauls</hi> poſte<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rity hanged, 9. Bones buried, 12. Giants, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 22.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 22 <hi>Davids</hi> Thankeſgiving for ſubduing his ene<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mies. <hi>Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 23 <hi>Davids</hi> laſt words, 1. His mighty men, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 8.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 24 People numbred 1300000, 9. 70000 dyed, 15 <hi>Araunah,</hi> 18. Plague ceaſed, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 25.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <pb n="22" facs="tcp:9621:14"/>
               <head>1. KINGS.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 <hi>ABiſhag,</hi> 3. <hi>Adoniah</hi> uſurpeth, 7. <hi>Solomon</hi> anoynted, 39. <hi>Adoniah</hi> flieth, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 50.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 <hi>Davids</hi> charge to <hi>Solomon,</hi> 1. <hi>Adoniah,</hi> 25. <hi>Io<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ab,</hi> 34. <hi>Shemei</hi> ſlaine, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 46.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 <hi>Pharoahs</hi> Daughter, 1. <hi>Gibeon,</hi> 5. Asketh wiſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dome, 9. Two Harlots, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 16.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 <hi>Solomons</hi> Princes, 2. Proviſion, 22. His great<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>neſſe, 26. Wiſedome, 29. Proverbs, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 32.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 5 <hi>Hiram</hi> bleſſeth God for <hi>Solomon,</hi> 7. Granteth his deſire, 9. <hi>Solomons</hi> workmen. <hi>Verſ.</hi> 13.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 6 The building of the Temple, 1. Gods promiſe, 12. The time of Building it, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 38.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 7 Thirteene yeares building his owne houſe, 1. <hi>Hirams</hi> curious workes in all the veſſels, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 15.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 8 Feaſt of Dedication, 1. <hi>Solomons</hi> Prayer, 23. Exceeding Sacrifices, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 63.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 9 Gods covenant with <hi>Solomon,</hi> 3. <hi>Hiram,</hi> 12. Cities built, 17. <hi>Cananites</hi> tributaries, 21. Na<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>vie, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 26.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 10 Queene of <hi>Sheba,</hi> 2. Her gifts, 10. <hi>Solomons</hi> wealth, 14. Throne, 18. Chariots, 26. Horſes, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 28.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 11 <hi>Solomons</hi> Idolatry, 4. Adverſaries, 14. <hi>Ierobo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>am</hi> appointed King over tenne Tribes, 31. <hi>Solo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mons</hi> end, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 43.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 12 <hi>Rehoboam,</hi> 1. <hi>Ieroboam,</hi> 12. <hi>Adoram</hi> ſlaine, 18. Warre forbid, 24. Two Calves, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 28.</item>
               <pb n="23" facs="tcp:9621:14"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 13 <hi>Ieroboams</hi> hand reſtored, 6. Young and old Prophet, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 14.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 14 Threats againſt <hi>Ieroboam,</hi> 10. <hi>Abiiah</hi> mourned for, 18. <hi>Ieroboams</hi> Sinne, 16. His end, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 15 <hi>Abiiam</hi> evill, 3. <hi>Aſa</hi> good, 11. Hired <hi>Bena<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dad,</hi> 18. End, 24. <hi>Nadab,</hi> 25. <hi>Baaſha, Verſ.</hi> 27.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 16 <hi>Elah,</hi> 6. <hi>Zimri,</hi> 9. <hi>Omri,</hi> 15. <hi>Ahab,</hi> 29. <hi>Ieri<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cho</hi> built, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 34.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 17 <hi>Eliiah,</hi> 1. <hi>Zarephah</hi> widow, 9. Her Sonne re<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtored to life, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 22.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 18 <hi>Eliiah</hi> meets <hi>Ahab,</hi> 16. <hi>Baals</hi> Prophets ſlaine, 40. Raine comes, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 45.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 19 <hi>Iezabel,</hi> 2. <hi>Eliiah</hi> flies to <hi>Horeb,</hi> 8. Comman<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ded to goe and anoynt <hi>Hazael, Iehu,</hi> and <hi>Eli<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſha, Verſ.</hi> 15.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 20 <hi>Benhadad</hi> twice overthrowne, 29. <hi>Ahab</hi> lets him goe, 34. Is threatned for it, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 42.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 21 <hi>Naboths</hi> Vineyard, 2. <hi>Ahab</hi> threatned, 21. Re<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>pents, 27. Spared, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 29.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 22 <hi>Ahabs</hi> falſe Prophets, 6. <hi>Micaiah,</hi> 15. <hi>Aha<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ziah,</hi> 40. <hi>Iehoſophats</hi> Life, 42. Death, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 50.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>2. KINGS.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 <hi>AHaziah</hi> ſendeth for <hi>Eliiah,</hi> two Captaines, 9.11. The third ſpared, 15. <hi>Iehoram, Verſ.</hi> 17.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 <hi>Eliiah</hi> taken up, 11. <hi>Eliſha</hi> ſucceedeth, 13. Di<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>vides <hi>Iordan,</hi> 14. Waters healed, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 21.</item>
               <pb n="24" facs="tcp:9621:15"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 <hi>Eliſha</hi> obtaines water for three Kings army, 20. <hi>Moab</hi> deſtroyed, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 24.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 Oyle increaſed, 5. <hi>Shunamites</hi> Sonne raiſed, 35. Pottage healed, 41. The loaves, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 42.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 5 <hi>Naaman</hi> commeth to the Prophet, 9. Is clean<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſed, 14. <hi>Gehezi</hi> a Leper, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 27.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 6 Iron ſwims, 6. <hi>Syrians</hi> counſell diſcloſed, 10. Their army led to <hi>Samaria,</hi> 19. Famine, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 25.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 7 Plenty, 16. Ruler trod to death in <hi>Samaria, Verſ.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 8 <hi>Shunamites</hi> land reſtored, 6. <hi>Benhaedad</hi> murthe<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>red, 15. <hi>Ioram,</hi> 16. <hi>Ahaziah, Verſ.</hi> 25.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 9 <hi>Iehu</hi> King, 13. Kils <hi>Ioram,</hi> 24. <hi>Ahazia,</hi> 27. <hi>Ie<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>zabell</hi> eaten with Dogs, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 36.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 10 Seventy of <hi>Ahabs</hi> Sonnes ſlaine, 7. All <hi>Baals</hi> Prieſts deſtroyed, 25. <hi>Iehoaz, Verſ.</hi> 35.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 11 <hi>Athaliah,</hi> 1. <hi>Ioaſh</hi> King, 12. <hi>Athaliah</hi> ſlaine, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 16.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 12 <hi>Iehoahaz</hi> repaireth the Temple, 5. Gave all the dedicated things to <hi>Hazael,</hi> 18. Is ſlaine, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 13 <hi>Iehoahaz,</hi> 1. Iſrael delivered by Prayer, 4. <hi>Io<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>aſh,</hi> 9. <hi>Ieroboam,</hi> 13. <hi>Eliſhas</hi> death, 14. Bones, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 21.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 14 <hi>Amaziah</hi> overcome of <hi>Iehoaſh,</hi> 12. Slaine, 19. <hi>Azariah,</hi> 21. <hi>Ieroboam, Verſ.</hi> 23.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 15 <hi>Azariah</hi> a Leper, 5. <hi>Iotham,</hi> 7. <hi>Zechariah</hi> ſlaine, 10. <hi>Shallum,</hi> 13. <hi>Menahen,</hi> 16. <hi>Pehaiah,</hi> 23. <hi>Pehah, Verſ.</hi> 27.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 16 <hi>Ahaz</hi> hyred <hi>Aſhur,</hi> 7. Sets vp an Altar, 12. Spoiles the Temple, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 17.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 17 <hi>Hoſhea</hi> carried to <hi>Aſſyria,</hi> 6. Their ſinnes, 9. God and Idols, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 33.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 18 <hi>Hezakiah</hi> gave tribute, 16. <hi>Rabſeceth</hi> raileth, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 35</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 19 <hi>Eſay</hi> Prophecieth againſt <hi>Senacherib,</hi> 6. 185000
<pb n="25" facs="tcp:9621:15"/> Slaine, 35. <hi>Senacherib</hi> ſlaine, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 37.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 20 To <hi>Hezekiahs</hi> life 15. yeares added, 6. Sunne goeth back, 11. <hi>Babilonians</hi> ſee his treaſures, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 13.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 21 <hi>Manaſſeh,</hi> 1. <hi>Amon,</hi> 19. <hi>Ioſiah, Verſ.</hi> 24.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 22 <hi>Ioſiah,</hi> 1. <hi>Hilkiah,</hi> 8. Booke, 10. <hi>Huldah, Verſ.</hi> 15.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 23 Covenant, 2. Deſtroyed Idolatry, 5. Paſſe<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>over, 21. Slaine, 29. <hi>Iehoaz,</hi> 31. <hi>Eliakim, Verſ.</hi> 34.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 24 <hi>Iehoiachim,</hi> 1. <hi>Iehoiacin,</hi> 6. <hi>Hieruſalem</hi> taken, 12. <hi>Zedekiah</hi> rebelled, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 25 <hi>Ieruſalem</hi> taken with <hi>Zedekiah,</hi> 4. Poore leſt, 12. <hi>Gedaliah</hi> ſlaine, 25. <hi>Iehoiacin</hi> advanced, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 28.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>1. CHRONICLES.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 <hi>ADams</hi> line to <hi>Noah,</hi> 1. <hi>Shems</hi> to <hi>Abra<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ham,</hi> 17. <hi>Edom, Verſe.</hi> 43.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 <hi>Iudah,</hi> 3. <hi>Ieſſe,</hi> 13. <hi>Caleb,</hi> 18. <hi>Hezron,</hi> 21. <hi>Ie<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rahmeel,</hi> 25. <hi>Caleb</hi> of <hi>Hur, Verſe.</hi> 50.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 <hi>David</hi> his line to <hi>Ieconiah,</hi> 1. His ſucceſſors, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 10</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 <hi>Hur,</hi> 1. <hi>Iabeſh,</hi> 9. <hi>Shelah,</hi> 21. Of <hi>Simeon,</hi> 24. Their conqueſt, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 41.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 5 <hi>Reubens</hi> poſterity, 1. <hi>Gad,</hi> 11. Halfe <hi>Manaſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſeh,</hi> 23. Captive to <hi>Aſſyria, Verſe.</hi> 26.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 6 <hi>Levi,</hi> 1. Prieſts, 4. <hi>Gerſhom,</hi> 16. <hi>Merari,</hi> 19. <hi>Kohath,</hi> 22. <hi>Aaron,</hi> 49. Cities, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 57.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 7 <hi>Iſſacar,</hi> 1. <hi>Benjamin,</hi> 6. <hi>Naphtali,</hi> 13. <hi>Manaſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſeh,</hi> 14. <hi>Ephraim,</hi> 
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>0. <hi>Aſher, Verſe.</hi> 30.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 8 <hi>Benjamin,</hi> 1. <hi>Saul</hi> and <hi>Ionathan, Verſe.</hi> 33.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 9 Who dwelt at <hi>Ieruſalem,</hi> 3. <hi>Saul</hi> and <hi>Ionathans</hi> poſterity, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 39.</item>
               <pb n="26" facs="tcp:9621:16"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 10 <hi>Sauls</hi> Death, 4. <hi>Iabeſh Gilead,</hi> 12. <hi>Sauls</hi> ſin, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 13.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 11 <hi>David</hi> King, 3. <hi>Ioab</hi> winneth <hi>Iebus,</hi> 6. <hi>Davids</hi> Worthies, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 10.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 12 The Armies that came to <hi>David</hi> to <hi>Zicklag</hi> and <hi>Hebron. Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 13 Arke brought home, 7. <hi>Vzzah</hi> ſtricken, 10. <hi>O<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>bed-Edom</hi> bleſſed, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 14.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 14 <hi>Hirams</hi> kindnes, 1. <hi>Davids</hi> wives, 3. Chil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dren, 4. Victor over <hi>Philiſtims, Verſe.</hi> 11.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 15 Arke brought to <hi>Sion,</hi> 3. Order of Prieſts, 17. <hi>Michol</hi> deſpiſed <hi>David, Verſe.</hi> 19.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 16 <hi>Davids</hi> Sacrifice, 1. Order of ſinging Pſalmes of thankes, 4. Officers to attend on the Arke, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 37.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 17 <hi>Davids</hi> Sonne ſhould build Gods houſe, 11. His Prayer and thankes, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 16.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 18 <hi>Davids</hi> victories, 1. <hi>Tou</hi> ſendeth Preſents, 9. Dedicated to God, 11. Garriſons in <hi>Edom, Verſe.</hi> 13.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 19 <hi>Davids</hi> meſſengers abuſed, 4. The <hi>Ammonites</hi> and <hi>Syrians</hi> overcome, 14. <hi>Shophach</hi> ſlaine, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 20 <hi>Rabbah</hi> taken, 1. Three Giants ſlaine by <hi>Da<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>vid</hi> and his men, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 4.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 11 <hi>Davids</hi> numbring of the People, 2. Puniſhed, 7. <hi>Ornan,</hi> 15. Plague ſtayeth, 27. <hi>David</hi> Sacri<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ficeth, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 28.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 22 <hi>David</hi> prepareth for the Temple, 3. Encoura<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ged <hi>Solomon</hi> and the Princes, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 6.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 23 Number and order of Levites. <hi>Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 24 Twenty foure Orders of Prieſt by lot, 18. Reſt of the Levites, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 25 Twenty foure Orders of Singers. <hi>Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <pb n="27" facs="tcp:9621:16"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 26 Diviſion of Porters, 1. Treaſures, 20. Officers and Iudges, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 29.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 27 Twelue Princes, 1. Heads of Tribes, 16. <hi>Da<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>vids</hi> Officers, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 25.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 28 <hi>Davids</hi> exhortation to all the Princes, 8. To <hi>Solomon,</hi> 9. Gives patterne of all, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 11.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 29 <hi>Davids</hi> bountifull offering, 4. And ſo of the Princes, 6. And People, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 9.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>2. CHRONICLES.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 <hi>SOlomon</hi> Sacrificeth at <hi>Gibeon,</hi> 6. Asketh wiſe<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dome, 10. His wealth, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 15.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 Labourers for Gods houſe, 2. Workmen and ſtuffe from <hi>Hiram, <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 11.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 Building, 1. Meaſures and Ornaments, 3. Che<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rubim, 10. Vayle, 14. Pillars, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 17.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 Altar, 1. Sea, 2. Ten Lavers, 6. Candleſtickes, 7. Inſtruments of Gold and Braſſe, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 16.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 5 Arke ſet in his place, 6. Innumerable Sacrifi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ces, 6. Cloud filled houſe, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 13.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 6 <hi>Solomons</hi> Prayer. <hi>Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 7 Fire from Heaven, 1. Great Sacrifices, 5. Feaſts, 8.6. Anſwer to <hi>Solomons</hi> prayer, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 12.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 8 <hi>Solomons</hi> Buildings, 2. His Tributaries, 7. Offi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cers, 10. Sacrifices, 12. Levites, 14. Navie, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 9 Queene of <hi>Sheba,</hi> 1. <hi>Solomons</hi> riches, 13. His end, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 31.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 10 <hi>Rehoboam</hi> King, 1. Tenne Tribes revolt, 16.
<pb n="28" facs="tcp:9621:17"/> 
                  <hi>Adoran</hi> killed, 18. <hi>Rehoboam</hi> flieth, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 11 Armies diſmiſſed, 4. Cities fortified, 5. Levits to <hi>Ieruſalem,</hi> 13. <hi>Rehoboams</hi> wives, 18. Children, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 21</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 12 <hi>Rehoboam</hi> forſaking God is ſpoyled by <hi>Shiſhac</hi> 9. Repents, 12. His end, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 16.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 13 <hi>Abiiah</hi> overcommeth <hi>Ieroboam,</hi> 15. The num<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ber ſlaine, 17. <hi>Abiiahs</hi> end, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 21.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 14 <hi>Aſa</hi> deſtroyes Idolatry, 3. Overcomes the <hi>E<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>thiopians,</hi> 13. Great ſpoyle, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 14.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 15 <hi>Azariahs</hi> prophecy, 2. All Iſraell ſweare to God, 14. <hi>Maacah</hi> put downe, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 16.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 16 <hi>Aſa</hi> ſeekes helpe of <hi>Benadad,</hi> 2. <hi>Hanani</hi> pri<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſoned, 10. Sought Phyſitians, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 12.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 17 <hi>Iehoſophat</hi> ſent to teach, 7. Feared, 10. Excee<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ding great, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 12.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 18 <hi>Iehoſophat</hi> joynes with <hi>Ahab,</hi> 1. <hi>Ramoth,</hi> 3. <hi>Zedekiah,</hi> 10. <hi>Micaiah,</hi> 12. <hi>Ahab</hi> ſlaine, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 34.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 19 <hi>Iehoſophat</hi> reproved, 2. Brought the people to God, 4. Sends Iudges, 5. And Levites, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 8.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 20 His Faſt, 3. Prayer, 6. <hi>Iahaziels</hi> prophecy, 14. <hi>Beracha,</hi> 26. Ioyned with <hi>Ahaziah, <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 35.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 21 <hi>Iehoram</hi> ſlew his Brethren, 4. Threats by <hi>Eli<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ah,</hi> 12. Bowels fall out, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 19.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 22 <hi>Ahaziah,</hi> 1. Slaine by <hi>Iohn,</hi> 9. <hi>Athaliah,</hi> 10 <hi>Ioaſh</hi> ſaved from death, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 11.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 23 <hi>Iehoiadah</hi> makes <hi>Ioaſh</hi> King, 11. <hi>Athaliah</hi> ſlain 15. Covenant, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 16.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 24 <hi>Ioaſh</hi> repareth Temple, 4. <hi>Iehoiadahs</hi> honorabl<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap> buriall, 16. <hi>Ioaſh</hi> ſlayes <hi>Z<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>chariah,</hi> 21. Is ſlaine, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 2<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 25 <hi>Amaziah,</hi> 1. Hired Iſrael, 6. Diſmiſſed, the<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap> ſpoyle, 13. <hi>Edom</hi> overcome, 14. Is overcome, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 22.</item>
               <pb n="29" facs="tcp:9621:17"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 26 <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>zziah,</hi> 1. Becommeth a Leper for offering in<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cenſe, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 27 <hi>Iotham</hi> proſpereth, 6. Overcommeth the <hi>Am<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>monits, <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 5.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 28 <hi>Ahaz</hi> burnt his children, 3. Sore afflicted, 5. <hi>Iſrael</hi> reſtore the captives, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 14.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 29 <hi>Hezekiah,</hi> 1. Reſtoreth religion, 2. Sacrifi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ceth, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 22.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 30 Paſſeover, 13. Great rejoycing, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 26.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 31 Idolatry deſtroyed, 1. Orders of Prieſts and Le<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>vits, 2. His ſincerity, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 32 <hi>Senacheribs</hi> blaſphemy, 14. Is deſtroyed, 21. <hi>Hezekiahs</hi> ſicknes, 24. Pride, 25. Humbled, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 26.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 33 <hi>Manaſſes,</hi> 1. Captive, 11. Humbled, 12. re<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>formed, 15. <hi>Amon</hi> ſlaine, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 24.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 34 <hi>Ioſiah</hi> reformed, 3. Booke read, 18. <hi>Huldah,</hi> 23. Covenant, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 31.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 35 Paſſeover, 1. <hi>Ioſiah</hi> ſlaine, 24. Lamentations of <hi>Jeremiah, <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 25.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 36 <hi>Iehoaz</hi> captive in <hi>Egypt,</hi> 4. <hi>Iehoiakim,</hi> 5. <hi>Ie<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>hoiacin,</hi> 9. <hi>Zedekiah.</hi>
               </item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>EZRA.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 <hi>CYrus</hi> proclamation for building Gods houſe, 1. All the veſſels delivered, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 7.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 Number that returne, 1. Prieſts that could not ſhew their Pedigree, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 62.</item>
               <pb facs="tcp:9621:18"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 Altar ſet up, 3. Offerings, 4. Foundation laid with joy and mourning, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 10.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 The Adverſaries procure letters from <hi>Artax<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>erxes</hi> to hinder the building, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 23.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 5 <hi>Haggai</hi> ſtirs up to build, 1. <hi>Tatnai</hi> writes to <hi>Darius</hi> to hinder it, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 6.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 6 <hi>Darius</hi> promotes the building, 6. Temple fini<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſhed, 14. Dedicated, 16. Paſſeover, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 19.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 7 <hi>Ezra</hi> with letters from <hi>Artaxerxes</hi> goes to <hi>Ie<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ruſalem,</hi> 6. Bleſseth God, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 27.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 8 Who came to <hi>Ieruſalem,</hi> 8. A faſt, 21. Trea<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſure delivered, 25. Weighed, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 33.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 9 <hi>Ezra</hi> faſteth and prayeth, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 6.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 10 Removing of ſtrange wives, 19. Their names, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 20.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>NEHEMIAH.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 <hi>NEhemiah</hi> faſteth for <hi>Ieruſalem,</hi> 4. Prayeth for favour with the King. <hi>Verſ.</hi> 11.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 <hi>Artaxerxes</hi> grant to <hi>Nehemiah,</hi> 6. He viewes <hi>Ieruſalem,</hi> 22. Incites to build, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 17.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 Names who builded, 8. And where. <hi>Through<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>out the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 Enemies ſcoffe. 2. And conſpire, 8. <hi>Nehemiah</hi> prayed, <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>. Armed, 13. Encouraged, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 5 Oppreſsors rebuked, 7. Covenant of reſtitu<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tion, 11. <hi>Nehemiahs</hi> Hoſpitality, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 17.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 6 <hi>Samballat</hi> with others hinder the building, 9. Wall finiſhed, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 15.</item>
               <pb n="31" facs="tcp:9621:18"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 7 Genealogie of all that returned, 6. Their ſub<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtance, 66. Gifts to the treaſury, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 70.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 8 The reading of the Law, 3. Not to mourne, 10. Feaſt of Tabernacles, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 16.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 9 A ſolemne Faſt, 1. Their prayer, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 6.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 10 Names of thoſe that covenant, 1. And what, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 29</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 11 Who dwelt at <hi>Ieruſalem,</hi> 1. And who in other Cities, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 12 Prieſts and Levits, 1. Dedication of the wall, 27. Officers appointed, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 44.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 13 Chambers clenſed, 4. Tithes, 10. Sabbath, 15. Strange wives reformed, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 23.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>ESTHER.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 <hi>AHaſuerus</hi> Feaſt, 3<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap> 
                  <hi>Vaſhti</hi> depoſed, 21. Husbands authority, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 22.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 <hi>Eſther</hi> Queen, 17. <hi>Mordecay</hi> diſcovereth trea<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſon, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 21.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 <hi>Haman</hi> advanced, 1. Is deſpiſed by <hi>Mordecay,</hi> 2. Seeks the Iewes deſtruction, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 6.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 <hi>Mordecay</hi> mourns, 1. <hi>Eſther</hi> after three dayes faſt reſolves to goe to the King, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 16.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 5 <hi>Eſther</hi> findes favour, 2. Bids the King to two banquets, 4. Gallowes for <hi>Mordecay, Verſ.</hi> 14.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 6 <hi>Ahaſuerus</hi> commands <hi>Haman</hi> to honour <hi>Mor<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>decay,</hi> 10. His fall foretold, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 13.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 7 <hi>Eſther</hi> accuſeth <hi>Haman,</hi> 6. He is hanged on the
<pb n="32" facs="tcp:9621:19"/> gallowes prepared for <hi>Mordecay, Verſ.</hi> 10.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 8 <hi>Mordecay</hi> advanced, 2. Letters ſent on behalfe of the Iewes, 11. Their joy, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 16.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 9 Iewes ſlay their enemies, 2. Another day, 13. <hi>Purim</hi> feaſting, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 10 <hi>Ahaſuerus</hi> his greatnes, 2. <hi>Mordecayes</hi> advance<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ment, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 3.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>IOB.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 <hi>IOb</hi> great, 3. Godly, 5. <hi>Sathan</hi> deſtroyes all his eſtate, 19. <hi>Job</hi> bleſſeth God, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 21.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 <hi>Sathan</hi> ſmites <hi>Iobes</hi> body, 7. He reproves his wife, 10. Three friends lament, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 12.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 <hi>Iob</hi> curſeth bitterly, 3. Wearie of his life, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 <hi>Eliphaz</hi> reproves <hi>Iobs</hi> hypocriſie, 6. Gods judgements on the wicked, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 8.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 5 Miſeries of wicked, 2. Gods chaſtiſements, 17. Godly happy, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 6 <hi>Iobs</hi> complaint of his affliction, 2. And of his friends, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 15.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 7 Short life, 1. And miſerable, 4. Complaint a<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gainſt God, 12. Confeſſeth his ſinne, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 8 <hi>Bildad</hi> chargeth <hi>Iob</hi> of wickednes, 6. Miſery of Hypocrits, 13. Righteous bleſſed, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 9 <hi>Iob</hi> confeſſeth Gods juſtice, 1. And power, 5. Condemnes himſelfe, 20. Innocent afflicted, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 30.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 10 <hi>Iobs</hi> complaint to God of his ſore affliction, 1.
<pb n="33" facs="tcp:9621:19"/> Craves ſome eaſe, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 11 <hi>Zophar</hi> accuſeth him of wickednes, 3. God wiſe, 6. Benefit of repentance, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 13.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 12 <hi>Iobs</hi> defence, 3. Gods mighty power, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 7.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 13 Their partialitie, 7. His confidence, 15. Pleads with God, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 23.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 14 Short life, 1. Vnrecoverable, 2. Waits for his change, 14. Man through ſin decayes, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 16.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 15 <hi>Eliphaz</hi> condemnes <hi>Iob,</hi> 2. Man uncleane, 14. Wicked curſed, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 24.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 16 <hi>Iob</hi> blames their unmercifulnes, 2. His wofull caſe, 7. Witnes, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 19.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 17 Their ſin, 2. And ignorance, 4. Righteous not diſmaid, 9. His hope in death, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 11.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 18 <hi>Bildad</hi> reproves <hi>Iobs</hi> impatiencie, 2. Calami<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ties of the wicked, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 5.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 19 <hi>Iob</hi> blames their crueltie, 2. His ſore vexati<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ons, 8. Hope of reſurrection, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 25.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 20 <hi>Zophar,</hi> 1. Ioy of Hypocrites ſhort, 5. Their wretched eſtate, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 7.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 21 <hi>Iob</hi> ſhewes the wickeds proſperity, 7. Yet de<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtroyed, 17. One dyeth, 23. judgement, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 30.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 22 <hi>Eliphaz</hi> accuſeth <hi>Iob,</hi> 5. Exhorts to repen<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tance, 21. With promiſe of mercy, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 23.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 23 <hi>Iob</hi> appeales to God, 3. His confidence, 10. Innocencie, 11. Gods decree unchangeable, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 13.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 24 Moſt wicked proſper till death, 1. Then their woe, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 17.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 25 <hi>Bildad</hi> ſhewes Gods majeſty, 2. None juſt be<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>fore him, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 4.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 26 <hi>Iob</hi> blameth <hi>Bildad,</hi> 2. Acknowledgeth Gods
<pb n="34" facs="tcp:9621:20"/> power unſearchable, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 5.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 27 <hi>Iobs</hi> confidence, 4. And innocency, 6. Hypo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>crites hope, 8. Their bleſſings to curſes, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 14.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 28 There is a naturall knowledge, 1. But wiſdome ſurpaſſeth, 12. Which is the feare of God, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 28.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 29 <hi>Iob</hi> bemoaneth his former proſperity, 2. His holy life, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 12.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 30 <hi>Iobs</hi> proſperity turned to adverſity. <hi>Through<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>out the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 31 <hi>Iob</hi> makes a ſolemne proteſtation of his inte<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>grity. <hi>Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 32 <hi>Elihu</hi> reproves <hi>Iob</hi> and his three friends, 2, 3. His zeale to ſpeake, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 33 He challengeth <hi>Iob,</hi> 5. Defends Gods procee<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ding, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 12.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 34 He chargeth <hi>Iob,</hi> 5. All Gods wayes juſt, 12. Man muſt be humbled to God, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 31.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 35 Mans good or evill touches not God, 3. Many cry and not heard, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 12.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 36 Gods wayes juſt, 6. <hi>Iobs</hi> ſin hinders Gods bleſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſing, 17. Gods workes to be magnified, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 24.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 37 God is to be feared for his workes, 1. His wiſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dome unſearchable, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 15.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 38 God convinceth <hi>Iob</hi> by his mighty workes of ignorance and frailtie.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 39 Gods workes in ſundry creatures is wonder<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>full. <hi>Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 40 <hi>Iobs</hi> humiliation, 4. <hi>Iobs</hi> weaknes, 9. <hi>Behe<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>moth, Verſ.</hi> 15.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 41 Gods great power in the Leviathan. <hi>Through<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>out the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <pb n="35" facs="tcp:9621:20"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 42 <hi>Iob</hi> yeelds, 6. His three friends pardoned, 9. His reſtoring, 10. Age, 16. Death, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 17.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>PSALMES.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 THe happines of the godly, 1. Vnhappines of the ungodly, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 4.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 Enemies of <hi>Chriſts</hi> Kingdome, 1. Rulers muſt kiſſe the Sonne, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 12.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 Security under Gods protection. <hi>Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 Exhortation to repentance, 4. Ioy in Gods favour, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 7.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 5 Prayer in confidence for the godly againſt the wicked. <hi>Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 6 Complaint of ſore ſicknes, 2. Tryumph againſt enemies, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 10.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 7 Prayer for defence, 1. Comfort againſt ene<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mies, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 10.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 8 Gods glory, 1. In mans dignity by creation, 5. And in <hi>Chriſt, <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 6.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 9 Thanks for deliverance, 1. Gods judgments right, 4. Prayer for his, 13. Againſt enemies, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 19.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 10 Pride of wicked, 2. Prayer againſt them, 12. With confidence, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 16.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 11 Confidence againſt wicked, 1. God loves the righteous, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 7.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 12 Help Lord, 1. God defends his fro<g ref="char:cmbAbbrStroke">̄</g> the wicked, 5
<pb n="36" facs="tcp:9621:21"/> Gods word as ſilver, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 6.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 13 How long, 1. His fervent deſire, 3. And con<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>fidence, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 14 The Foole, 1. None good, 3. Eate up my peo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ple, 4. <hi>Iſrael</hi> ſhall be glad, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 7.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 15 Who ſhall dwell, 1. The upright in heart and life, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 2.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 16 The Lord is my portion 5. Hope of reſurrecti<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>on, 10. And life Eternall, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 11.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 17 Prayer to be delivered from Enemies, 8. Their proſperity and pride, 10. His hope, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 15,</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 18 Thankes for Victories and other bleſſings, <hi>Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 19 Gods glory in his creatures, 1. Excellency of the word, 7. Prayer for grace, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 14.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 20 Prayer for the King, 1. Confidence in God, 5. Some in Chariots, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 7.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 21 Thanks for victory, 1. Confidence for further ſucceſſe, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 7.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 22 Prayer in great affliction, 1. A type of <hi>Chriſt,</hi> 6. Thanks, 23. Confidence, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 27.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 23 What bleſſed ſtate under Gods protection, <hi>Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 24 Who be true Chriſtians, 4. They muſt receive <hi>Chriſt, <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 7.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 25 Prayer with confidence for grace, 1. Gods goodnes to his, 12. Their afflictions, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 17.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 26 Comfort of a good conſcience, 2. Appeale to God, 6. Love to Gods houſe, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 8.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 27 Faith in God nouriſhed, 1. And teſtified, 3. Stirre up to Prayer, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 14.</item>
               <pb n="37" facs="tcp:9621:21"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 28 Fervent deſire to be heard againſt enemies, 2. With confidence, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 7.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 29 Princes muſt glorifie God, 1. His power in thunder, 4. Majeſty and mercy, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 11.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 30 Thanks for deliverance, 1. Moment in anger, 5. Turned my mourning, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 11.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 31 Confidence in prayer in ſore affliction, 1. O how great is thy goodnes, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 19.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 32 Bleſſing in forgivenes, 1, Confeſſion, 5. Par<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>don, 5. Inſtruct others, 8, Ioy of righteous, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 11.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 33 Praiſes, 1. Gods powerfull providence, 6. Confidence in God, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 34 Stirre up to thanks, 1. Bleſſed that truſt, 8. Angels encamp, 7.6. Favor to the righteous, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 19.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 35 Prayer againſt enemies, 1. Their ill rewarding. 12. He moves God to mercy, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 17.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 26 Wickednes of the wicked, 1. God excellent in mercy, 7. Prayer, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 10.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 37 Fret not at the wickeds proſperity, 1. State of Righteous better in life and death, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 12.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 38 Complaint of ſore affliction, 2. Confidence, 15. And Prayer, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 21.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 39 Shortnes, 5. And vanity of mans life, 6. Pray<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>er for releaſe, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 12.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 40 <hi>David</hi> a type of <hi>Chriſt</hi> in confidence and obe<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dience, 6. Prayer againſt enemies, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 14.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 41 Conſider the Poore, 1. Enemies reproach, 5. Friends againſt him, 9. Prayer with co<g ref="char:cmbAbbrStroke">̄</g>fidence, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 10.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 42 Zeale to Gods houſe, 4. Comforts himſelfe with confidence in Gods helpe, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 8.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 43 Prayer to be delivered from wicked, 1. And
<pb n="38" facs="tcp:9621:22"/> reſtored to the Temple, 3. Encourageth himſelf, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 4</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 44 Gods former mercies, 1. Their preſent calami<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ty, 9. Yet conſtancy, 17. Prayer for ſuccour, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 23.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 45 Song of <hi>Chriſt,</hi> 2. And his Church, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 10.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 46 Confidence in Gods preſence, 1. Exhortation to behold Gods works, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 8.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 47 All people exhorted to entertaine <hi>Chriſts</hi> Kingdome. <hi>Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 48 Ornaments and priviledges of the Church un<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>der the type of <hi>Zion. Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 49 Parable of the vanity of all earthly proſperity, 4. Hope of Reſurrection, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 15.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 50 Falſe and true worſhip, 8.14. Hypocriſie and true obedience, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 16.23.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 51 <hi>Dauids</hi> repentance, 3. Prayer for the Church, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 52 <hi>Doegs</hi> ſinne, 2. And deſtruction, 5. Righteous rejoyce at it, 6. <hi>Davids</hi> confidence, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 9.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 53 None good, 3. Feare where no feare, 5. Com<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>fort of the Faithfull, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 6.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 54 Prayer to be delivered from wicked, 1. And confidence for helpe, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 4.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 55 Sore affliction, 4. Not mine enemy, 12. Prayer with confidence, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 16.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 56 Like the former, 1. In God will I praiſe his word, 4. Thy vowes are upon me, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 12.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 57 Prayer with confidence, 3. My heart is fixed, 7. Be thou exalted, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 11.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 58 Wicked Iudges, 1. Wicked as deafe Adder, 4. Before your pots, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 9.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 59 Cruelty of enemies, 2. Like dogs, 6. Slay them
<pb n="39" facs="tcp:9621:22"/> not, 11. But I will ſing of thy power, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 16.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 60 Thou hadſt caſt us off, 1. Now a Banner, 4. Into <hi>Edom,</hi> 9. Through God, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 12.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 61 Prayer with confidence from former mercies, 3 For the King prepare mercy, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 7.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 62 He is my rocke, 2. Wait on him, 8. If riches encreaſe, ſet not, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 10.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 63 My fleſh longs for thee, 1. Enemy fall, 10. God<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ly rejoyce, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 11.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 64 Preſerve me, 1. Whet tongues, 3. God ſhall ſhoot, 7. Righteous rejoyce, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 10.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 65 Praiſe waits, 1. Bleſſed whom thou chuſeſt, 4. Gods power, 6. And goodnes, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 9.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 66 Gods mighty works, 3. Pay vowes, 13. If I regard iniquity, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 67 Prayer for increaſe of Gods Kingdome, 1. And his bleſſings, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 6.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 68 Prayer for Gods favour to his people, 3. Led Captivity captive, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 69 Save me, 1. Zeale, 9. Gall for meat, 21. Out of Booke, 28. Thanks for deliverance, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 30.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 70 Prayer for ſpeedy deliverance to the joy of the godly. <hi>Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 71 His confidence, 1. Enemies inſolency, 11. For<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſake not when old, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 72 Prayer for <hi>Solomon;</hi> his a type of <hi>Chriſts</hi> King<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dome, 1. Bleſſeth God, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 73 Temptation overcome, 17. Deſtruction of wicked, 18. Whom have I, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 25.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 74 Sanctuary waſted, 3. Prayer for helpe, 10. Con<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>fidence in Gods power, 13. And covenant, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 20.</item>
               <pb n="40" facs="tcp:9621:23"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 75 Thanks, 1. Pride of wicked, 5. Their deſtruc<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tion, 7. Cup of wine, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 8.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 76 In <hi>Iudah</hi> God is knowne, 1. Vow and pay unto the Lord, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 11.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 77 Combat with diſtruſt, 7. Victory by medita<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tion on Gods workes, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 11.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 78 Story of Gods dealings with <hi>Iſrael,</hi> 12. Hee choſe <hi>Iudah,</hi> 68. And <hi>David, <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 70.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 79 Defiled thy Temple, 1. Prayer for help againſt enemies, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 8.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 80 Prayer for Church, 3. Parable of a Vine, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 8.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 81 Exhortation to praiſe, 1. <hi>Iſrael</hi> would none of me, 11. O that my people, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 13.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 82 Iudges exhorteth, 3. And reproved, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 5.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 83 Prayer againſt oppreſſors, 9. Like <hi>Oreb</hi> and <hi>Zeeb, <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 11.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 84 How pleaſant, 1. Bleſſed in Gods houſe, 4. One day better, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 10.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 85 Turne us O God, 4. He will ſpeake peace, 8. Mercy and truth meet, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 10.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 86 Prayer for Gods favour, 4. Complaint of proud, 14. Deſires a token, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 17.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 87 Glory of the Church, 3. And of the members thereof, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 5.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 88 Complaint of ſore afflictions with little or no mention of comfort, <hi>Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 89 Praiſes for Gods mercies to his, 1. I have found <hi>David,</hi> 20. Yet afflicted, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 38.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 90 Shortnes of life, 10. Prayer for the right uſe, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 12.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 91 The exceeding felicity of the faithful. <hi>Through<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>out the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <pb n="41" facs="tcp:9621:23"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 92 Sabbath Title, Thanks for Gods judgements and mercies, <hi>Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 93 The Lord raigneth in majeſty, 1. Holines of Gods houſe, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 5.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 94 Vengeance againſt wicked, 1. Chaſtiſed bleſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſed, 12. God defends his, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 22.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 95 Exhortations to thanks for Gods greatnes and goodnes, 1. Not to tempt God, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 8.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 96 Exhortation to thanks, 1. Give glory, 7. He ſhall judge righteouſly, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 10.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 97 The Lord reigneth, 1. Majeſty and holines of Gods houſe, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 2.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 98 Sing a new Song, 1. Let the Sea roare, 7. Hils rejoyce, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 8.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 99 The Lord raigneth, 1. <hi>Samuel</hi> among his Prophets, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 6.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 100 Exhortation to praiſe God for his greatnes &amp; goodnes everlaſting. <hi>Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 101 Duties of a good Governour. <hi>Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 102 Prayer for the afflicted, 1. Praiſe unto God, 21. As a veſture ſhalt thou change them, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 26.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 103 Thanks for Gods great benefits, 1. And the continuance of them, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 17,</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 104 Praiſe of Gods majeſty, 1. And mercy, 23. And wiſedome in all his workes, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 24.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 105 Gods goodnes to <hi>Iſrael</hi> from <hi>Abrahams</hi> time till <hi>Canaan. Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 106 Gods mercies to <hi>Iſrael</hi> often provoking him, 7. <hi>Phinees</hi> zeale, 30. Afflicted pray, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 47.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 107 Gods providence in all diſtreſſes, 6. Thanks, 8.
<pb n="42" facs="tcp:9621:24"/> Wiſe obſerve it, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 43.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 108 Awake my harpe, 2. Praiſes for ſubduing e<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nemies, 3. <hi>Gilead, <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 8.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 109 Complaint againſt wicked, 2. And prayer, 6. <hi>Iudas,</hi> 8. Confidence, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 31.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 110 Kingdome, 2. Prieſthood, 4. Conqueſt, 5. And paſſion of <hi>Chriſt, <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 7.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 111 Praiſe of Gods workes, 2. Of glory, 3. And grace, 7. Feare of the Lord, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 10.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 112 Great proſperity of the godly, 2. Wicked gnaſh at it, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 10.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 113 Praiſe God for his greatneſſe and goodneſſe. <hi>Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 114 <hi>Iudah</hi> Gods Sanctuary, 2. <hi>Iordan,</hi> 3. Hils, 4. Earth tremble at Gods preſence, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 7.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 115 Not to us, 1. Idols vaine, 5. Truſt in <hi>God,</hi> 9. He will bleſſe, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 13.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 116 I love the Lord, 1. What ſhall I render, 12. Pay my vowes, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 14.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 117 Exhortation to praiſe <hi>God</hi> for his mercy and truth for ever. <hi>Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 118 Praiſes for protection, 6. Better to truſt, 8. <hi>Chriſt</hi> corner ſtone, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 22.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 119 Excellency of the word, 9. <hi>Davids</hi> heavenly meditation and practiſe. <hi>Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 120 Wicked tongue, 3. Woe is me that I ſojourne in <hi>Meſech, <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 5.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 121 Safety under <hi>Gods</hi> protection, 3. Sun ſhall not ſmite thee, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 6.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 122 Reioycing and prayer for <hi>Ieruſalem</hi> the Church. <hi>Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <pb n="43" facs="tcp:9621:24"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 123 As the eyes of a Maid waite, 2. Prayer from contempt, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 3.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 124 If the Lord, 1. Thankes for great delive<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rance. <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 6.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 125 They that truſt in the Lord ſafe, 1. Wicked periſh, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 5.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 126 Ioy and thanks for returne out of captivity, 2. Sow in teares, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 5.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 127 Except the Lord build, 1. Bleſſing of Chil<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dren, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 3.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 128 Bleſſed that feare <hi>God. Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 129 Many times afflicted <hi>Iſrael,</hi> 1. Her haters curſed, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 5.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 130 Out of the depths, 1. I waite for the Lord, 5. Shall redeeme <hi>Iſrael, <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 8.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 131 Humility as a weaned childe, 2. Let <hi>Iſrael</hi> hope, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 3.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 132 Lord remember <hi>David,</hi> 1. His care and prayer for the Arke, 8. Promiſes to <hi>Sion, <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 11.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 133 Communion of Saints bleſſed. <hi>Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 134 Miniſters exhorted to praiſe <hi>God. Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 135 Praiſes of <hi>Gods</hi> mercy, 4. Power, 6. And judg<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ments on <hi>Egypt,</hi> 9. <hi>Og,</hi> 11. Idols vaine, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 16.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 136 Thankeſgiving to <hi>God,</hi> 1. His mercie endu<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>reth for ever. <hi>Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 137 Profeſſion in <hi>Babel,</hi> 5. <hi>Edom,</hi> 7. And <hi>Babel</hi> curſed, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 8.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 138 Praiſes of <hi>Gods</hi> mercies, 1. And word, 2. Con<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>fidence in God. <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 7.</item>
               <pb n="44" facs="tcp:9621:25"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 139 Gods all-ſeeing providence, 7. I hate them that hate thee, 21. Trie me, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 23.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 140 Prayer for deliverance from wicked, 1. Con<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>fidence, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 12.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 141 Prayer as incenſe, 2. Let the righteous ſmite me, 5. Mine eyes to thee, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 8.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 142 In trouble all comfort in Prayer. <hi>Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 143 Prayer in affliction with confidence for grace. <hi>Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 144 Praiſe and prayer, 1. What is man, 3. Bleſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſed whoſe God is the Lord, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 15.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 145 Gods Kingdome glorious, 12. And gracious, 14. Holy in all his workes, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 17.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 146 Truſt not in Princes, 3. Gods favours to his, 5. Poore afflicted, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 9.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 147 Praiſes for Gods care generall, 3. And ſpe<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ciall, 12. Statutes to <hi>Iſrael, <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 19.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 148 Exhortations to all creatures to praiſe God. <hi>Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 149 Praiſes for Gods love to his Church for ſo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>veraignty<g ref="char:punc">▪</g> 
                  <hi>Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 150 Exhortations to all manner praiſes by every living creature. <hi>Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <pb n="45" facs="tcp:9621:25"/>
               <head>PROVERBS.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 VSes of Proverbs, 2. If ſinnes intice, 10. Wiſedome calls to repentance, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 Benefits of the word, 1. To eſcape evill men and women, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 12.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 Gaine of wiſedome incomparable, 2. Many ſpeciall duties. <hi>Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 Inſtruction of Parents, 1. Fruit of wiſdome, 7. Way of wicked, 14. Keepe thy heart, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 23.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 5 Miſchiefe by whoredome, 4. Comforts of marriage, 15. Wife loving and kind, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 19.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 6 Surety, 1. Idle, 5. Miſchievous, 12. Seven hate<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>full, 16. Law a light, 23. Whore, 24. Iealouſie, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 34.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 7 Wiſedome thy ſiſter, 4. Allurements of whore, 14. Danger by her, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 23.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 8 Excellency of wiſedome, 11. Hearken to her, 32. Such as ſo doe bleſſed, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 34.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 9 Wiſedomes Feaſt, 2. And follies Banquet, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 17.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 10 Righteous and wicked, 6. Wiſe and foole, 13. Rich and poore, 15. Tongue, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 11 Righteous and Wicked, 5. Hypocrites, 9. Surety, 15. Liberall, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 25.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 12 Righteous and Wicked, 5. Foole, 15. Lying<g ref="char:punc">▪</g> 18. Slothfull, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 24.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 13 Sonne, 1. Sluggard, 4. Righteous, 5. Pride, 10. Prudent, 16. Word, 13. Correction, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 24.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 14 Woman, 1. Scorner, 6. Fooles, 7. Preſuming, 12
<pb n="46" facs="tcp:9621:26"/> Labor, 23. Feare of God, 27. Sound heart, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 30.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 15 Tongue, 2. Sacrifice of wicked, 8. Good hart, 14 Love, 1<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>. Folly, 21. Counſell, 22. Covet, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 27.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 16 Prepar<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap> 
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>f heart, 1. Pride, 5. Mercy and Truth, 6. King, 12. Wiſe, 14. Good ſpeech, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 24.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 17 Quiet, 1. Servant, 2. Speech, 7. Gift, 8. Reproofe 10. Strife, 14. Friend, 17. Fooliſh <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>on, 25. ſile<g ref="char:cmbAbbrStroke">̄</g>ce, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 28</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 18 Fooliſh words, 7. S<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>oth, 9. Pride, 12. Wounded ſpirit, 14. Gift, 16. Lot, 18. Offended, 19. Wife, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 22</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 19 Raſh, 2. Poor, 4. Falſ witnes, 5. Wife, 13. Chaſtiſe 18. wrath, 19 counſel, <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>0. ſlothful, 24. ſcorner, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 25</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 20 Wine, 1. King, 2. Sluggard, 4. Child, 11. Buyer, 14. Counſell, 18. Curſe, 20. Revenge, 22. Age, 29. Wound, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 30.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 21 Kings heart, 1. Iuſtice, 3. Pride, 4. Contentio<g ref="char:cmbAbbrStroke">̄</g>, 9. Gift, 14. Paſtime, 17. Silence, 23. Sloth, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 25.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 22 Good name, 1. Prudent, 3. Child, 6. Sow Iniqui<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ty, 8. Rod, 15. Friendſhip, 24. Surety-ſhip, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 26.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 23 Teperancy, 1. riches flee, 4. correctio<g ref="char:cmbAbbrStroke">̄</g>, 13. Wiſe ſo 15. riotous, 20. buy truth, 23. whore, 27. wine, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 30</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 24 Envy not, 1. Wiſe, 5. Counſel, 6. Honey, 13. luſt all ſeven times, 16. Feare God and King, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 21.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 25 Ki<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>g<g ref="char:punc">▪</g> 1. Word in ſe<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                     <desc>••</desc>
                  </gap>on, 11. Vain confidence, 14. F<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>ele enemy, 21. Bad wife, 24. Vain glory, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 27</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 26 Curſe, 2. Fool<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                     <desc>••</desc>
                  </gap>. 3. Sloth, 13. Buſi-body, 17. Cont<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>ntion, 21 H <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>red, <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>4. Tongue, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 8.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 27 B<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                     <desc>••</desc>
                  </gap>ſt not, 1. E<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                     <desc>••</desc>
                  </gap>y, 4. Friend, 6. Prudent, 12. D <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="3 letters">
                     <desc>•••</desc>
                  </gap>ing, 15. Foole, <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>2. Thri<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>t, 23. Honor, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 24.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 28 Ma<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>y Princ<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                     <desc>••</desc>
                  </gap>, <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>. Wicked, 3. Vſury, 8. Hide ſin, 1<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>. Prince, 16. <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                     <desc>••</desc>
                  </gap>ouke, 23. Liberality, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 27.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 29 King, 4. Scorner, 8. Wiſe, 11. Correction, 15. No
<pb n="47" facs="tcp:9621:26"/> Viſion, 18. Servant, 19. Angry, 22. Abhom. <hi>Verſ.</hi> 27.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 30 <hi>Agurs</hi> poverty nor riches, 8. Foure generations, 11. Many ſecrets and wonders, 18. Stately, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 29.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 31 <hi>Lemuel,</hi> 1. Mercy &amp; juſtice, 9. Vertuous wife, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 10</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>ECCLESIASTES.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 ALL Vanity, 2. Nothing new, 10. King try<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ed all, 12. Much wiſdome much griefe, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 17</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 Pleaſures, 1. Buildings, 4. Poſſeſſions vaine, 7. One end to all, 15. Labour, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 22.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 Seaſon for all, 1. Gods worke perfect, 14. Iuſt and uniuſt iudged, 17. Man and beaſt one con<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dition, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 19.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 Oppreſſion, 1. Envy, 4. Two better, 9. Fooliſh King, 13. Second childe, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 15.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 5 Looke to thy foot, 1. Vowes. 2. Oppreſſe, 8. Riches, 10. Right uſe of <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>arthly, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 6 No uſe of goods, 2. Children, 3. Age, 6. Wandring deſires, 9. What ſhall be, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 10.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 7 Good name, 1. Mourning, 2. Patience, 8. Wiſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dome, 11. Over iuſt, 16. Wicked woman, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 26.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 8 King, 2. Gods Providence, 6. Sinner not pro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſper, 12. Vſe of Gods bleſſings, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 15.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 9 Like to all, 2. Life and death, 3. Comfort of Earthly, 7. Wiſe poore man, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 15.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 10 Dead flyes, 1. Folly in Ruler, 5. Speech, 12. King a childe, 16. Curſe not the King, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 11 Bread on waters, 1. Sowing, 4. Rejoyce O yong man, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 9.</item>
               <pb n="48" facs="tcp:9621:27"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 12 In youth remember, 1. Preachers care, 9. Words as goades, 11. Feare of God, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 13.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>Song of SOLOMON.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 CHurches love, 4. Deformity, 5. <hi>Chriſts</hi> love and commendation, 9. Both joy, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 12.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 Mutuall love, 2. Hope and calling of the Church, 8. <hi>Chriſts</hi> care, 14. Churches hope, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 16.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 Churches temptation, 1. Victory, 4. She glorieth in <hi>Chriſt, Verſe.</hi> 6.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 CHRIST commends, 1. And ſhews love, 8. Church prayes for grace, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 16.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 5 <hi>Chriſts</hi> voice, 1. Church awake, 2. Seeks, 6. Finds at laſt, 7. Commends <hi>Chriſt, Verſe.</hi> 10.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 6 Churches faith, 2. <hi>Chriſt</hi> commends her, 4. And his love to her, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 10.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 7 <hi>Chriſt</hi> commends her, 1. Her Faith and de<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſire to him. <hi>Verſe.</hi> 10.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 8 Her love to him, 1. Iealouſie, 6. Gentils called, 8. She prayes for his comming, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 14.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <pb n="49" facs="tcp:9621:27"/>
               <head>ISAIAH.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 OXe, 3. No ſoundnes, 6. Small remnant, 9. Sacrifices hated, 11. Waſh, 16. Iudgments, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 20.28.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 Law on Zion, 3. Lofty looks, 11. Idols caſt to the Moules, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 Staffe of bread, 1. Iudah fallen, 8. Well with the righteous, 10. Oppreſſion, 12. Pride of wo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>men, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 16.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 Seven women, 1. Comfort by <hi>Chriſts</hi> King<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dome, 2. Spirit of burning, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 4.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 5 Song of vineyard, 1. Wo to covet, 8. Riot, 11. Oppreſſion, 23. Hiſſe for a nation, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 26.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 6 Seraphims, 2. Send me, 8. Make fat, 10. A tenth ſhall returne, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 13.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 7 <hi>Ahaz</hi> refuſeth a ſigne, 12. Virgin conceive, 13. <hi>Aſſyria</hi> a raſour, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 8 <hi>Syria</hi> and <hi>Iſrael</hi> ſubdued by <hi>Aſhur,</hi> 4. Sancti<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>fie the Lord, 13. To the Law, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 9 Vnto us a Childe is borne<g ref="char:punc">▪</g> 6. Iudgement on <hi>Iſrael</hi> for Pride, 9. Hypocriſ<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>e, 17. Impenitency, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 10 Wo to oppreſſing <hi>Aſhur,</hi> 12. The rod ſhake it ſelfe, 15. Remnant, 20. As the ſand, 22. Pro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>miſes of deliverance, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 25.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 11 Wolfe and Lambe, 6. Root of <hi>Ieſſe,</hi> 10. Gen<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tils called and Iewes reſto<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>ed, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 12.16.</item>
               <pb n="50" facs="tcp:9621:28"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 12 Thankſgiuing for Gods mercies. <hi>Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 13 Deſolation of <hi>Babylon. Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 14 Mercy to <hi>Iſrael,</hi> 1. Tryumph over <hi>Babel,</hi> 4. <hi>Aſhur</hi> and <hi>Paleſtine</hi> threatned, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 25.29.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 15 Burden of <hi>Moab. Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 16 <hi>Moab</hi> exhorted, 3. Threatned, 7. Bewailed, 9. The judgment thereof, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 14.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 17 <hi>Damaſcus</hi> and <hi>Ephraim</hi> threatned, 1. Woe to the enemies of Gods people, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 12.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 18 Woe to <hi>Ethiopians,</hi> 1. Gathered to <hi>Zion, Verſ.</hi> 7.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 19 Burden of <hi>Egypt,</hi> 1. Princes fooles, 11. Their Calling, 19. Vnion with <hi>Iſrael</hi> and <hi>Aſhur, Verſ.</hi> 25.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 20 Reproachfull Captivity of <hi>Egipt</hi> and <hi>Ethiopia</hi> by <hi>Aſhur. Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 21 Againſt <hi>Babylon,</hi> 9. <hi>Edom,</hi> 11. <hi>Arabia, Verſ.</hi> 13.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 22 Againſt <hi>Iudah,</hi> 4. Called to mourning, 12. <hi>Shebna,</hi> 15. <hi>Eliakim</hi> choſen, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 23 Againſt <hi>Tyre,</hi> 1. Their converſion to God, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 24 Againſt all other Lands, 1. Remnant ſhall praiſe God for his judgements, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 13.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 25 Thankeſgiving, 1. Feaſt of fat, 6. All teares wiped away, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 8.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 26 Song of Salvation, 1. Open the gates, 2. Let mercy be ſhewed, 10. Other Lords, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 13.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 27 Gods care for his Vineyard, 3. In meaſure, 8. Iniquity of <hi>Iacob</hi> purged, 9. Trumpet blow, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 13.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 28 Woe to the pride, 1. Remnant, 5. Vomiting, 8.
<pb n="51" facs="tcp:9621:28"/> Line upon line, 10. Stone in <hi>Zion,</hi> 16.6. Pro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>vidence, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 29.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 29 Woe to <hi>Ariel,</hi> 1. Spirit of ſleep, 10. Wiſe pe<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>riſh, 14. Deafe ſhall heare, 18. Promiſes, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 22.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 30 Vaine hope in <hi>Egipt,</hi> 2. Obſtinacy, 10. Sweet promiſes, 18. Iudgments, 27. Tropheck, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 33.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 31 Vaine hope in <hi>Egipt,</hi> 1. Egyptians men, 3. <hi>Aſſyria</hi> fallen, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 8.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 32 Bleſſing of Chriſts Kingdome, 1. Deſolation. 9. Reſtoring promiſed, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 15.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 33 Iudgments againſt enemies, 1. Priviledges of godly, 15. Scribe, 18.6. Our law-giver, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 22.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 34 Gods vengeance on the enemies of his <hi>Church. Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 35 Promiſes to the Church, 1. Lame leape, 6. — Returne promiſed, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 10.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 36 <hi>Rabſeceth</hi> bla<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>phemeth, 20. They anſwer him not, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 21.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 37 <hi>Hezekiahs</hi> prayer, 15. <hi>Senacheribs</hi> judgment, 24, Promiſes to Zion, 30. <hi>Senacherib</hi> ſlaine, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 38.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 38 <hi>Hezekiah</hi> ſick, 1. Prayer, 3. Fifteen yeares, 5. Sun goes back, 8. Thankſgiving, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 9.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 39 <hi>Hezekiah</hi> ſhewes his treaſures, 2. <hi>Iſaiah</hi> tells him all ſhall be carried to <hi>Babel, Verſ.</hi> 6.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 40 Voice of a cryer, 3. All fleſh graſſe, 6. Goſpel, 9. Gods omnipotency, 12. Comforts to <hi>Iacob, Verſ.</hi> 28.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 41 Gods greatnes, 4. Vanity of Idols, 7. Gods merciful promiſes, 10. Idols vain abominatio<g ref="char:cmbAbbrStroke">̄</g>, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 22</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 42 <hi>Chriſts</hi> office, 1. Meeknes, 3. Thanks for the Goſpel, 10. Peoples incredulity, 20 Di<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>obed. <hi>Verſ.</hi> 23</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 43 Promiſes of deliverance, 2. Out of <hi>Babel,</hi> 5.
<pb n="52" facs="tcp:9621:29"/> Their ſinne, 22. His mercy, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 25.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 44 Promiſes, 3. Folly of Idol-makers, 9. Exhor<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tation to turn, 22. Thanks for Gods mercy and power, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 23.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 45 <hi>Cyrus,</hi> 1. God alone, 5. His power, 7. Mercy to his, 15. Idols vain, 16. Every knee bow to God, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 23.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 46 <hi>Babels</hi> Idols, 1. God ſaveth his to the end, 3. Idols cannot helpe, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 7.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 47 Gods vengeance on the <hi>Caldeans</hi> for cruelty, 6. Pride, 7. Not reſiſtable, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 11.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 48 <hi>Iſraels</hi> obſtinacy, 4. For my own ſake, 11.9. He teacheth to profit, 17. O that thou hadſt, 18. Goe out of <hi>Babel, Verſ.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 49 <hi>Chriſt</hi> refuſed, 4. Sent to Gentils, 6. Promiſes, 8. Reſtor. of Church, 18. Kings nurſe fathers, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 23.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 50 The Iews forſaken is of themſelves, 1. <hi>Chriſt</hi> able and willing to ſave, 2. His obedience and ſuffering, 5. Truſt, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 10.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 51 Exhortation to hearken to Chriſt, 1. His pow<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>er to ſave, 9. <hi>Iſraels</hi> affliction, 17. Deliverance, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 22.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 52 Exhortation to obedience, 6. To receive the Miniſters, 7. How beautifull, 7. Chriſts King<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dome exalted, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 13.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 53 Chriſts ſufferings, 4. The ſucceſſe thereof, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 10.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 54 Church encreaſed, 1. Safety, 4. Certaine deli<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>verance, 7. Beauty, 11, Preſervation, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 14.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 55 Calling to believe, 1. And repent, 6. Their happines, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 12.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 56 Exhortation to holineſſe, 1. Sabbath, 2.
<pb n="53" facs="tcp:9621:29"/> Eunuchs, 4. Blind watchmen, 10. Greedy dogs, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 11.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 57 Bleſſed death of Righteous, 1. Whoriſh Ido<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>laters, 3. Promiſe to contrite. 15. No peace, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 21.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 58 Hypocrits faſt, 3. Promiſe to godlineſſe, 8. And to keeping the Sabbath, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 13.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 59 Fruit of Sinne, 2. Salvation from God alone, 16. Spirit not depart, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 21.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 60 Churches glory by the Gentiles, 3. And rich bleſſings thereon after afflictions, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 15.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 61 Chriſts office, 1. Precious promiſes, 4. The bleſſed ſeed, 9. Robe of righteouſneſſe, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 10.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 62 Promiſes, 2. Miniſters office to preach, 6. And prepare for Chriſt, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 10.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 63 Chriſts victory, 1. Mercy to his, 7. Churches prayer, 15. Made us erre, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 17.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 64 Churches prayer, 1. And thanks, 8. Their af<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>fliction, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 10.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 65 Gentiles called, 1. Iewes rejected, 2. Rem<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nant, 8. Wicked plagued, 12. Godly bleſſed, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 13.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 66 Humble bleſſed, 2. Hypocrits curſed, 3. Com<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>forts to faithfull, 10. Iudgments, 15. Gentils called, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 19.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>IEREMIAH.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 <hi>IEremies</hi> calling, 5. Viſions, 11. Iudgments a<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gainſt <hi>Iudah,</hi> 15. Be not diſmaid, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 17.</item>
               <pb n="54" facs="tcp:9621:30"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 Gods kindnes, 2. Their revolt, 5. Two evils, 13. Calamities Idoll, 15. Preſumption, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 35.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 Yet returne, 1. <hi>Iudah</hi> worſe then <hi>Iſrael,</hi> 8. Pro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>miſes, 12. As a wife, 20. Confeſſe of ſinne, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 23.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 Returne, 1. Sweare, 2. Follow, 3. Iudgments, 7. Waſh thy heart, 14. My bowels, 19. Great deſolation, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 23.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 5 Find a man, 1. Great man, 5. Adultery, 7. Impi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ety, 11. Contempt of God, 19. All ſtates corrup<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ted, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 26.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 6 <hi>Ieruſalem</hi> viſited for her ſins, 6. Peace, 14. Old way, 16. Incenſe abhom. 20. Sword from North<g ref="char:punc">▪</g> 
                  <hi>Verſ.</hi> 22.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 7 Temple, 4. <hi>Shiloh,</hi> 14. Pray not, 16. Queen of hea<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ven, 18. They will not heare, 27. Trophet, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 32.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 8 Death choſen, 3. Sins, 5. We are wiſe, 8. Aſha<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>med, 9. Healed hurt, 11. No balme, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 22.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 9 Lamentation for ſin, 1. And judgment, 10. Not to glory in man, 23. <hi>Ieruſalem</hi> heaps, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 11.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 10 God not as Idols, 6. His power, 12. Paſtors, brutiſh, 21. Correct in judgment, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 24.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 11 Breakers of Covenant curſed, 3. Pray not, 14. Like a Lamb, 19. <hi>Anathoth, Verſ.</hi> 23.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 12 Wickeds proſperity, 2. Treachery of his Bre<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>thren, 6. Heritage forſaken, 10. Returne, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 16.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 13 Linnen girdle, 4. Every bottle filled, 12. King humble, 18. Can the <hi>Ethiopian, Verſ.</hi> 23.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 14 Famine, 1. Pray not, 11. Falſe Prophets pe<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>riſh, 15. <hi>Ieremiah</hi> bewailes them, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 17.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 15 Though <hi>Moſes,</hi> 1. Rejection, 2. Their ſpite, 10, <hi>Jeremies</hi> prayer, 15. Favour promiſed, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 19.</item>
               <pb n="55" facs="tcp:9621:30"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 16 Iewes ruine, 4. Worſe then Fathers, 12. Fi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſhers, 16. Hunters, <hi>ibid.</hi> Double for idolatry, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 17 Captivity for ſin, 4. Vaine cruſt, 5. Who bleſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſed, 7. Mockers, 15. Sabbath, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 21.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 18 Potter, 2. Iudgments for idolatry, 11. <hi>Iere<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>miah</hi> prayes againſt his enemies, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 19.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 19 Veſſell broken, 10. So is <hi>Iudah,</hi> 11. Citie de<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>filed as <hi>Trophech, Verſ.</hi> 13.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 20 <hi>Paſhur,</hi> 1. <hi>Ieremiahs</hi> complaint, 7. Confidence, 11. Thanks, 13. Curſing, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 14.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 21 Anſwer to <hi>Zedekiah</hi> of his deſtruction, 4. And of the Kings houſe, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 11.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 22 Exhort to repentance, 3. Promiſes, 4. Threats, 5. <hi>Shallum,</hi> 11. <hi>Iehoiakim,</hi> 18. <hi>Coniah, Verſ.</hi> 24.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 23 Promiſes, 3. The Lord our righteouſneſſe, 6. Againſt falſe Prophets, 13. Burden of the Lord, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 33.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 24 Figs good and bad, 2. Captives reſtored, 6 <hi>Zedekiah</hi> and the reſt deſtroyed, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 8.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 25 Preaching of the Prophets deſpiſed, 3. After 70. yeares <hi>Babels</hi> deſolation, 12. Cup of wine to all, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 15.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 26 <hi>Ieremiah</hi> taken, 8. And acquit, 16. Example of <hi>Micah,</hi> 18. <hi>Vriah</hi> ſlaine, 23. <hi>Ahikam, Verſ.</hi> 24.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 27 Bonds ſent to the Nations, 3. To <hi>Zedekiah,</hi> 12. Falſe Prophets, 14. Veſſels goe to <hi>Babel, Verſ.</hi> 22.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 28 <hi>Hananias</hi> falſe Propheſie, 2. Breaks <hi>Ieremies</hi> yoke, 10. Iron yoke, 13. <hi>Hananiah</hi> dyeth, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 17.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 29 <hi>Ieremie</hi> writes to <hi>Babel,</hi> 4. After 70 returne, 10. <hi>Ahab</hi> and <hi>Zedekiah,</hi> 21. <hi>Shemaiah, Verſ.</hi> 24.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 30 A Booke writ of returne, 2. Which ſhalbe gra<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>cious,
<pb n="56" facs="tcp:9621:31"/> 10. Many promiſes, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 31 Promiſes, 2. <hi>Rahel,</hi> 15. <hi>Ephraim</hi> repented, 18. Chriſt, 22. New covenant, 31. Stable, 35. Church, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 38.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 32 <hi>Ieremie</hi> priſoned, 2. Buyes a field. 9. His pray<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>er, 17. Captivitie, 28. Returne, 37. Pretious promiſes, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 40.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 33 Returne, 7. Promiſes, 8. Chriſt our righteouſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>neſſe, 15. Covenant ſtable, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 34 Captivity threatned, 2. Servants ſet free, 10. Returne, 11. Iudgment denounced, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 17.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 35 <hi>Rechabits,</hi> 2. Iewes diſobedience, 14. Threat<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ned, 17. <hi>Rechabites</hi> bleſſed, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 19.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 36 <hi>Baruch</hi> writes, 4. And reades the Roll, 10. King burns it, 23. A new copy, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 32.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 37 <hi>Zedekiah</hi> ſends to <hi>Ieremy</hi> to pray, 4. <hi>Chaldeans</hi> ſhall return, 8. <hi>Ieremy</hi> impriſoned, 15. Favor, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 21.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 38 Dungeon, 6. <hi>Ebed-Melech,</hi> 11. <hi>Zedekiah</hi> con<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ferrs with him, 14. Which is concealed, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 27.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 39 <hi>Ieruſalem</hi> taken, 2. <hi>Zedekiahs</hi> eyes put out, 7. Poore left, 10. Favour to <hi>Ier<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>my,</hi> 12. <hi>Ebed-Me<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lech</hi> delivered, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 16.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 40 <hi>Ieremy</hi> goes to <hi>Gedaliah,</hi> 6. So the Iewes al<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſo, 8. <hi>Iſhmaels</hi> conſpiracy, 14. Not beleeved, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 16.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 41 <hi>Gedaliah</hi> ſlaine, 2. <hi>Iſhmael</hi> eſcapeth, 15. <hi>Ioha<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nan</hi> minds to goe to <hi>Egipt, Verſ.</hi> 17.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 42 <hi>Iohanan</hi> ſeeks counſell, 2. Their diſſimulation, 20. Threatned to periſh, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 22.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 43 All goe to <hi>Egipt,</hi> 7. <hi>Ieremy</hi> prophecieth <hi>Egipts</hi> ruine by <hi>Nebuchadnezzar, Verſ.</hi> 11.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 44 Idolatry in <hi>Egipt</hi> threatned, 11. We will not
<pb n="57" facs="tcp:9621:31"/> obey, 16, Iudgments, 26. <hi>Egipt</hi> threatned, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 30.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 45 <hi>Baruch</hi> diſmaid, 3. Is comforted, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 4.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 46 Againſt <hi>Egipt,</hi> 2. Comforts to Gods people, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 27.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 47 Deſtruction of the <hi>Philiſtims. Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 48 <hi>Moabits</hi> fall, 1. And riſing againe, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 47.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 49 <hi>Ammon,</hi> 2. <hi>Edom,</hi> 8. <hi>Damaſcus,</hi> 23. <hi>Kedar,</hi> 28. <hi>Hazor,</hi> 30. <hi>Elam</hi> reſtored, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 39.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 50 <hi>Babels</hi> deſtruction, 2. <hi>Iſrael</hi> delivered, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 34.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 51 <hi>Babels</hi> fall, 4. <hi>Secaiah</hi> caſts the writing into <hi>Emphrates</hi> in token thereof, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 63.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 52 <hi>Ieruſalem</hi> taken, 7. <hi>Zedekiahs</hi> eyes put out, 11. <hi>Ieruſalem</hi> burnt, 13. <hi>Iehoiakim</hi> advanced, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 32.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>LAMENTATIONS.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap:</hi> 1 <hi>IEruſalems</hi> miſery for ſin, 8. Remembred her pleaſures, 15. God righteous, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap:</hi> 2 <hi>Ieremy</hi> laments, 1. Complaines to God of their miſeries, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap:</hi> 3 Complaint, 1. Hope, 24. Confeſſion, 42. Pray<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>er for deliverance, 55. And vengeance, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 64.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap:</hi> 4 <hi>Zions</hi> complaint, 1. Confeſſion, 13. <hi>Edom</hi> threatned, 21. <hi>Zion</hi> comforted, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 22.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap:</hi> 5 A pittiful complaint of <hi>Zion</hi> in Prayer to God. <hi>Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <pb n="58" facs="tcp:9621:32"/>
               <head>EZEKIEL.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 THe viſion of foure Cherubins, 4. Of the foure wheeles, 15. Of the glory of God, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 26</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 <hi>Ezekiels</hi> Commiſſion, 3. Inſtruction, 6. Roll full of woes, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 9.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 Roll eaten, 2. He is incouraged, 4. Watchman, 17. Mouth ſhut and opened, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 26.27.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 Type of a ſiege, 1. His proviſion ſhewed the ſore famine, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 9.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 5 Type of haire, 1. Iudgments on <hi>Ieruſalem</hi> for rebellion; Sword famine ſcattering, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 12.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 6 Deſtruction of <hi>Iſrael,</hi> 3. A Remnant bleſſed, 8, Faithfull lament their calamity, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 11.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 7 End is come, 2. Remnant mourne, 16. Sanctu<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ary defiled, 20. Chaine for Captivity, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 23.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 8 In a Viſion Imagery at <hi>Ieruſalem,</hi> 5. At <hi>Ta<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>muz,</hi> 14. Worſhip the Sun, 16. Gods ven<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>geance, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 9 Mourners marked, 4. Reſt deſtroyed, 5. God will not be ent<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>eated, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 10.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 10 Viſion of Cherubins and coale of fire, <hi>Through<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>out the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 11 Wicked Princes, 1. <hi>Ez<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>kiels</hi> prayer, 13. Rem<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nant ſaved, 16. Wicked plagued, 21. <hi>Ezekiel</hi> to <hi>Caldea, Verſ.</hi> 24.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 12 <hi>Ezekiels</hi> removing a type of the Captivity, 3. His trembling a type, 19. Viſion is neere, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 28.</item>
               <pb n="59" facs="tcp:9621:32"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 13 Lying Prophets, 2. Vntempered morter, 10. Sow pillows, 18. Iudgments, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 14 Idolaters in heart, 3. Repentance enjoyned, 6. If <hi>Noah, &amp;c.</hi> 14. Foure iudgements, 21. Rem<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nant, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 22.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 15 The Vine tree unfit for uſe, 4. So <hi>Ieruſalem</hi> rejected, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 6.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 16 Gods love to <hi>Iſrael,</hi> 6. Childe in blood, 9. <hi>Ieruſalems</hi> whoredome, 15. <hi>Sodom</hi> and <hi>Samaria,</hi> 46. Covenant, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 60.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 17 Two Eagles, 2. Princes led Captive to <hi>Babel,</hi> 12. Cedar of the Goſpell planted, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 22.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 18 Parable of ſowre grapes, 2. Sinner dye, 4. Iuſt ſcape, 9. Gods way equall, 25. He loves not the death, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 32.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 19 Lyons whelps taken, 4. <hi>Ieruſalem</hi> a Vine wa<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſted, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 12.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 20 God will not anſwer, 3. Rebellions from <hi>Ae<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>gipt</hi> to <hi>Canaan,</hi> 6. Promiſes of Reſtoration, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 34.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 21 <hi>Ieruſalem</hi> deſtroyed, 47. Sighing, 6. Sharp ſword, 9. Two wayes, 16. <hi>Ie<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ruſale<g ref="char:cmbAbbrStroke">̄</g>
                  </hi> &amp; <hi>Ammon</hi> deſtroyed by the <hi>Caldeans, Verſ.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 22 Many ſins of <hi>Ieruſalem,</hi> 3. Fornace, 18. Falſe Prophets, 25. All ſtates corrupted, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 30.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 23 <hi>Aholah</hi> and <hi>Aholibah,</hi> 4. Shamefull adulteries, 20. Fearfull judgments, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 46.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 24 <hi>Ieruſalem</hi> a ſeething pot, 3. Quite burnt, 9. <hi>Ezekiel</hi> not mourning for his wife a ſigne, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 24.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 25 Againſt <hi>Ammon,</hi> 3. <hi>Moab,</hi> 8. <hi>Edom,</hi> 12. <hi>Phi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>liſtims, Verſ.</hi> 15.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 26 <hi>Tyrus</hi> ſacked by <hi>Nebuchadnezzar,</hi> 4. Princes of the Sea tremble at her fall, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 15.</item>
               <pb n="60" facs="tcp:9621:33"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 27 Riches of <hi>Tyrus</hi> by Merchandize, 3. Her ſore fall, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 27.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 28 Prince of <hi>Tyrus</hi> pride, 2. And fall, 7. Againſt <hi>Zidon,</hi> 21. <hi>Iſrael</hi> reſtored, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 24.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 29 <hi>Egipt</hi> deſtroyed, 9. Reſtored, 13. Baſ<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap> King<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dome, 14. <hi>Nebuchadnezzars</hi> reward, 20. <hi>Iſrael</hi> reſtored, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 24.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 30 Deſolation of <hi>Egipt</hi> by <hi>Babel. Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 31 Glory of <hi>Aſſyria,</hi> 3. The fall thereof for pride, 10. The like deſtruction of <hi>Egipt, Verſ.</hi> 18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 32 Lamentation for <hi>Egipt,</hi> 2. The fall of the o<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ther uncircumciſed Nations, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 33 Watchman, 2. Gods juſt dealing, 20. <hi>Ieruſa<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lem</hi> ſmitten, 21. Prophet mockers, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 30.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 34 Ill Shepheards, 2. God keeps his ſheepe, 10. Fat, 16. Chriſt promiſed, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 23.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 35 Againſt Mont <hi>Zeir</hi> for hatred of <hi>Iſrael. Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 36 Promiſes for reſtoring <hi>Iſrael,</hi> 3. Of Chriſts Kingdome, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 25.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 37 Dry bones revived, 10. Two ſticks united, 16. Of Chriſts Kingdome, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 22.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 38 Againſt <hi>Gog</hi> for invading <hi>Iſrael,</hi> 3. Fearefull plagues, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 39 <hi>Iſraels</hi> victory over <hi>Gog,</hi> 2. <hi>Hamon Gog,</hi> 11. Feare, 17. <hi>Iſrael</hi> plagued, 23. Reſtored, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 25.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 40 <hi>Ezekiels</hi> viſion of the gates, 6. Tables, 39. Chambers, 44. Porch, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 48.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 41 Meaſures, Parts, Chambers and Orna<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ments of the Temple. <hi>Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <pb n="61" facs="tcp:9621:33"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 42 Chambers of the Prieſts, 13. Their uſes, 14. Outward Court, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 19.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 43 Viſion, 2. Exhortation to Repentance, 10. Ob<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſervation of the law of the houſe, 11. Altar, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 44 Eaſt gate for the Prince, 3. No uncircumciſed, 7. Sonnes of <hi>Zadok,</hi> 15. Ordinances for Prieſts, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 17.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 45 Land for the Sanctuary, 1. Citie, 6. Prince, 7. Ordinances for Sacrifices, 13. And Feaſts, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 21.25.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 46 Orders for Prince and People, 1. His Inheri<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tance, 16. Courts for boyling and baking, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 47 Waters increaſing, 1. Their vertue, 8. Borders and diviſion of the Land by lot, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 13.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 48 Portions of the twelue Tribes, 1. Sanctuary, 8. Citie, 15. Prince, 21. Meaſures for 12. Gates, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 30.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>DANIEL.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 DANIEL with three others proſper with Pulſe, 15. King found none like wiſe, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 19.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 <hi>Nebuchadnezzars</hi> Dreame forgot, 5. Told, 31. Interpreted by <hi>Daniel,</hi> 37. His advancing, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 48.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 Three young men preſerved in the Fire, 25. King bleſſeth God, 28. Maketh a Decree, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 29.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 <hi>Nebuchad.</hi> Dreame, 5. <hi>Daniel</hi> interpreteth it, 20. King as a Beaſt, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 33.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 5 <hi>Balſhazar</hi> ſeeth an Hand writing, 5. <hi>Daniel</hi> readeth it, 25. Monarchy to the <hi>Medes, <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 31.</item>
               <gap reason="missing" extent="2 pages">
                  <desc>〈2 pages missing〉</desc>
               </gap>
            </list>
            <list>
               <pb n="64" facs="tcp:9621:34"/>
               <head>AMOS.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 IVdgements againſt <hi>Syria,</hi> 3. <hi>Philiſtim.</hi> 6. <hi>Ty<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rus,</hi> 9. <hi>Edom,</hi> 11. <hi>Ammon, Verſ.</hi> 13.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 Againſt <hi>Moab,</hi> 1. <hi>Iudah,</hi> 4. <hi>Iſrael,</hi> 6. Gods be<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nefits, 9. Their ſinne, 13. and Puniſhment, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 14.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 Gods righteous judgements for <hi>Iſraels</hi> Sinne. <hi>Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 Reproofe for Oppreſſion, 1. Idolatry, 4. Incor<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rigeableneſſe, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 6.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 5 Lamentation for <hi>Iſrael,</hi> 2. Exhortation to Re<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>pentance, 4. Hypocriticall ſervice rejected, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 21.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 6 <hi>Iſraels</hi> wantonneſſe plagued with deſolation, 7. Their incorrigeableneſſe, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 12.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 7 Graſhoppers, 1. Fire, 4. Plumbe-line, 7. <hi>Ama<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ziah,</hi> 10. Gods judgements againſt him, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 16.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 8 <hi>Iſraels</hi> end by a Basket of fruit, 1. Oppreſſion 4. Famine of the Word, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 11.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 9 Certaine deſolation, 1. <hi>Davids</hi> Tabernacle re<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtored, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 11.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 10 Iudgements againſt <hi>Edom</hi> for Pride, 3. Wrong to <hi>Iacob,</hi> 10. Salvation to <hi>Sion, Verſ.</hi> 17.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>IONAH.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 IONAH flying from God, 3. Is caſt into the Sea, 15. Swallowed by a Fiſh, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 17.</item>
               <pb n="65" facs="tcp:9621:34"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 Prayer out of the Fiſhes belly, 2. Deliverance thereupon, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 10.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 Preacheth at <hi>Nineveh,</hi> 4. They repent, 5. God ſpareth them, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 10.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 <hi>Ionah</hi> repining at Gods mercy is reproved by the ſimilitude of a Gourd, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 10.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>MICAH.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 GODS wrath againſt <hi>Iacob</hi> for Idolatry, 7. Exhortation to Mourning, <hi>Verſes</hi> 16.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 Oppreſſion, 2. Lamentation, 4. <hi>Iacob</hi> reſtored, <hi>Verſes</hi> 12.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 Princes cruelty, 2. Prophets falſhood, 5. Both ſecure, 11. <hi>Zion</hi> ploughed, <hi>Verſes</hi> 12.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 Churches glory, 1. Peace, 3. Kingdome, 8. and Victory, <hi>Verſes</hi> 13.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 5 <hi>Chriſts</hi> birth, 2. Kingdome, 4. Conqueſt, <hi>Verſes</hi> 8.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 6 Gods controverſie for Vnkindneſſe, 4. Igno<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rance, 6. Injuſtice, 10. And Idolatry, <hi>Verſes</hi> 16.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 7 Church complaines, 1. Truſts in God, 7. T<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>y<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>umpheth, 8. Shee is comforted, <hi>Verſes</hi> 14.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>NAHVM.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 GODS glory, power and goodneſſe to his, and wrath againſt the wicked. <hi>Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <pb n="66" facs="tcp:9621:35"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 Gods fearefull and victorious Armies againſt <hi>Niniveh. Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 Miſerable ruine of <hi>Niniveh</hi> compared with <hi>No</hi> in Aegypt, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 8.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>HABAKVK.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 COmplaint of Sinne, 3. Puniſhment by the <hi>Caldeans</hi> againſt the wicked, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 6.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 Live by Faith, 4. <hi>Caldeans</hi> plagued for many Sinnes, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 5.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 <hi>Habakuks</hi> Prayer, 1. Gods majeſty, 3. His trembling and rejoycing in God, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 16.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>ZEPHANIAH.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 GODS ſevere judgements againſt <hi>Iudah</hi> for divers Sinnes. <hi>Throughout the whole.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 Exhort. to Repentance, 1. Iudgements againſt <hi>Philiſtims,</hi> 4. <hi>Moab</hi> and <hi>Ammon,</hi> 8. <hi>Ethiopia,</hi> 12 <hi>Aſſyria, Verſ.</hi> 13.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 Woe to <hi>Ieruſalem,</hi> 1. Waite on God for Salva<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tion, 8. and rejoyce therein, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 14.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>HAGGAI.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ch<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>p</hi> 1 REproofe for not building the Temple, 4. Ex<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>hort. to build it, 8. Promiſe of Gods aſſi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtance, <hi>Verſes</hi> 13.</item>
               <pb n="67" facs="tcp:9621:35"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Ch<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>p</hi> 2 Encouragements to build, 4. The ſecond Tem<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ple more glorious, 9. Promiſes to <hi>Zerubabel, Verſes</hi> 23.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>ZECHARIAH.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 EXhortation to Repent. 3. Red Horſes, 8. Jealous for <hi>Ieruſalem,</hi> 14. Foure hornes and foure Carpenters, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 18.20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 <hi>Ieruſalem</hi> meaſured, 2. <hi>Zion</hi> redeemed, 7. Pro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>miſes to <hi>Ieruſalem, <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 10.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 <hi>Ioſhua,</hi> 1. Church reſtored, 7. CHRIST the branch, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 8.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 Golden Candleſticke, 2. <hi>Zerubabels</hi> foundati<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>on, 9. Two O<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>ives two anoynted ones, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 12.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 5 Flying Rowle, 2. Curſe of Theeves and Swea<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rers, 3. Ephah, 6. Finall damnation of <hi>Babi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>lon, <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 11.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 6 Foure Chariots, 1. <hi>Ioſhua</hi> crowned, 11. Type of Chriſt the branch, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 12.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 7 Captives faſting reproved, 5. Their ſinne was the cauſe of their Captivitie, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 14.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 8 Promiſes for reſtoring <hi>Ieruſalem,</hi> 4. Exhorta<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>i<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>on to build, 9. Obedience, 21. Church inc<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                     <desc>••</desc>
                  </gap>a<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſed, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 23.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 9 God defends his Church, 1. R<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>joyce for <hi>Chriſts</hi> comming, 9. Peace victory, defence, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 14.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 10 God gives raine not Idols, 1. God viſi<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>ed his flocke for Sinne, 5. Shewes great favour, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 10.</item>
               <pb n="68" facs="tcp:9621:36"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 11 Deſtruction of <hi>Ieruſalem,</hi> 2. Shep heards, 8. Staffe of beauty and bands, 10. Idoll Shepheard, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 17.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 12 <hi>Ieruſalem</hi> a trembling, 2, <hi>Iudah</hi> victoriouſly reſtored, 6. Great mourning, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 11.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 13 Fountaine opened, 1. Falſe Prophets, 2. Death of <hi>Chriſt,</hi> 7. Triall of a third part, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 8.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 14 <hi>Ieruſalem</hi> ſore waſted, 2. Enemy deſtroyed, 12. Remnant reſtored, 16. Spoyles holy, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 20.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>MALACHY.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 <hi>ISraels</hi> unkindneſſe, 6. Abuſe of Gods wor<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſhip, 7. Prophaneneſſe, 12. Snuffed, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 13.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 Reproofe of Prieſts, 2. Covenant with <hi>Levi,</hi> 5. <hi>Iudahs</hi> Idolatry, 11. Adultery, 14. Infidelity, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 17.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 <hi>Chriſts</hi> meſſenger, 1. Great ſin of Gods people, 5 Provocations to Repent, 7. Godly bleſſed, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 16.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 Wicked plagued, 1. Godly bleſſed, 2. Exhorta<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tion to remember the Law, 4. <hi>Eliiahs</hi> co<g ref="char:cmbAbbrStroke">̄</g>ming, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 5.</item>
            </list>
            <trailer>Thus farre the Old Teſtament.</trailer>
         </div>
         <div type="table">
            <pb n="69" facs="tcp:9621:36"/>
            <head>A TABLE OF THE NEW TESTAMENT.</head>
            <list>
               <head>MATTHEVV.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 <seg rend="decorInit">T</seg>He Genealogie, 1. Of Chriſt his Birth, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 Wiſe men, 1. <hi>Aegypt,</hi> 13. <hi>Ra<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>chel,</hi> 18. <hi>Nazareth, <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 23.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 <hi>Iohn</hi> Preached, 1. Vipers, 7. Bap<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tized CHRIST, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 13.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 <hi>Christ</hi> tempted, 1. <hi>Zabulon,</hi> 13. Taught, 17. Foure called, 18. Healed, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 23.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 5 Bleſſed, 3. Salt, 13. Light, 14. Law, 17. Kill, 21. Altar, 23. Adultery, 27. Revenge, 38. Love 43. Be perfect, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 45.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 6 Almes, 1. Prayer, 5. Faſt, 16. Treaſure, 19. Ey<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap> 22. Mammon, 24. No thought, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 25.</item>
               <pb n="70" facs="tcp:9621:37"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 7 Mote, 3. Dogs, 5. Aske, 7. Doe, 12. Gate, 13. Tree, 17. Lord, 21. Rocke, 24. Sand, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 26.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 8 Leper, 2. Centurion, 5. Healed, 16. Foxes, 20. Sea, 24. Gargarens, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 28.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 9 Palſie, 2. <hi>Matthew,</hi> 9. Faſt, 14. Ruler, 18. Iſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſue, 20. Blind, 27. Dumbe, 32. Healed, 35. Har<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>veſt, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 37.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 10 Twelve, 1. Sent, 7. <hi>Sodome,</hi> 15. Wife, 16. Flee, 23. Feare not, 26. Denyeth, 33. Loſe, 39. Prophet, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 41.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 11 <hi>Iohn,</hi> 2. <hi>Elias,</hi> 14. Corazin, 21. Wiſe, 25. Come to me, 28. My yoke, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 29.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 12 Sabbath, 1. Reade, 20. Belzebub, 24. Vipers, 34 <hi>Ionas,</hi> 39. Spirit, 43. Mother, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 46.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 13 Sower, 3. Parables, 10. Yee ſee, 13. Heart groſſe, 15. Tares, 24. Muſtard-ſeed, 31. Leven, 33. Treaſure, 44. Pearles, <hi>ibid.</hi> Net, 47. Scribe, 52. Carpenter, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 54.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 14 <hi>Herodias,</hi> 3. Healed, 14. 5000 fed, 15. Chriſt prayed, 22. <hi>Peter</hi> ſinkes, 30. Touched hemme, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 36.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 15 Waſh, 2. Lips, 5. What defileth, 11. Ditch, 15. Cananite, 22. Dumbe, 30. 4000 fed, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 32.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 16 Signe, 1. Leaven, 6. <hi>Peter,</hi> 16. Keyes, 19. Satan, 23. Winne world, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 26.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 17 Transfiguration, 1. <hi>Elias,</hi> 10. Divell, 14. Fa<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſting, 21. Chriſt betrayed, 22. Tribute, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>4.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 18 Childe, 2. Offences, 7. Tell him, 15. Bind, 18. Forgive, 21. Cruell Servant, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 28.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 19 Divorce, 3. Eunuchs, 12. Children, 13. Young man, 16. Rich, 23. An hundred-fold, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 29.</item>
               <pb n="71" facs="tcp:9621:37"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 20 Labourers, 1. Penny, 9. Chriſt fore-warnes, 17. Greateſt, 20. Two blinde, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 30.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 21 Hoſanna, 9. Temple, 12. Heal<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                     <desc>••</desc>
                  </gap>. 14. Babes, 16. Fig-tree, 19. <hi>John,</hi> 25. Two Sonnes, 28. Vine<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>yard, 33. Stone, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 42.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 22 Wedding, 2. <hi>Caeſar,</hi> 15. Reſur<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>ection, 23. Com<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mandement, 36. Lord, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 44.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 23 <hi>Moſes</hi> ſeate, 2. <hi>Rabbi,</hi> 8. Woes to Hypocrites, 14. Sweare, 16. Phariſes tythe, 23. Tombes, 27. Henne, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 37.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 24 Signes, 3. Warres. 6. Love cold, 12. Falſe Chriſts, 24. <hi>Noah,</hi> 37. Signe of Sonne of man, 30 Watch, 42. Servants, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 45.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 25 Virgin<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>, 1. Talents, 14. Laſt Iudgement, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 31.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 26 Ointment, 6. <hi>Iudas,</hi> 14. Paſſeover, 17. O<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>e Barly, 21. Lords Supper, 26. Garden, 36. Ar<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>raigned, 37. <hi>Peter</hi> denyes, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 69.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 27 <hi>Iudas,</hi> 3. Paſſion, 16. <hi>Pilates</hi> wife, 19. Chriſt. 27. Revealed, 39. Buried, 57. Seale, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 66.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 28 Reſurrection, 6. Goe teach and Baptize, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 19.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>MARKE.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 <hi>BAptist,</hi> 3. Chriſt tempted, 13. Foure cal<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>led, 16. Divell, 23. Feaver, 30. Healed, 32. Leper, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 40.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 Palſie, 2. <hi>Levi,</hi> 14. Whole, 17. Faſt. 18. Wine 22. Sabbath, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 23.</item>
               <pb n="72" facs="tcp:9621:38"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 Dryed hand, 1. <hi>Herodias,</hi> 6. Chriſt healed all, 10. Twelve, 14. <hi>Belzebub,</hi> 22. Blaſphemy, 28. Mother, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 31.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 Seed, 3. All in Parables, 11. Candle, 21. Mea<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſure, 24. Seed, 26. Parable, 33. Storme, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 37.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 5 Legion, 2. Swine, 11. <hi>Iairus,</hi> 22. Iſſue of bloud, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 25.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 6 Carpenter, 3. Twelue, 7. Duſt, 15. <hi>Baptiſts</hi> head, 16. Five thouſand, 36. Sea, 48. Healed, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 55;</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 7 Waſh, 2. <hi>Korban,</hi> 11. Defiles, 15. Crums, 24. Epphata, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 34.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 8 Foure thouſand, 1. Signe, 11. Leaven, 15. Blind 24. <hi>Peter,</hi> 29. Satan, 33. Croſſe, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 34.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 9 Transfiguration, 2. <hi>Elias,</hi> 11. Faſt, 29. Beleeve, 24. Greateſt, 34. Offend, 42. On our part, 48. Salt, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 49.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 10 Divorced, 2. Children, 13. Good, 18. Rich, 23 One hundred-fold, 30. <hi>Zebede,</hi> 35. Lordſhip, 42 Blind, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 46.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 11 Colt, 2. <hi>Hoſanna,</hi> 5. Temple. 11. Fig-tree, 13 Beleeve, 23. Forgive, 25. Authority, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 28.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 12 Vineyard, 1. Stone, 10. <hi>Caeſar,</hi> 14. Reſurrec<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tion, 18. Commandement, 28. Lord, 35. Wid<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dow, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 40.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 13 Signes, 4. Endure, 13. <hi>Daniel,</hi> 14. Shortned, 20. Chriſts ſecond comming, 24. Watch, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 33.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 14 <hi>Math.</hi> 26. <hi>Luke,</hi> 22. <hi>Iohn, Verſ.</hi> 13.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 15 <hi>Math.</hi> 27. <hi>Luke,</hi> 23. <hi>Iohn, Verſ.</hi> 18, 19.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 16 <hi>Math.</hi> 28. <hi>Luke,</hi> 24. <hi>Iohn, Verſ.</hi> 20.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <pb n="73" facs="tcp:9621:38"/>
               <head>LVKE.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 PReface, 1. <hi>Iohn,</hi> 13. <hi>Eliza</hi> bleſſeth, 42. <hi>Ma<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ries</hi> ſong, 46. <hi>Zacharies</hi> ſong, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 48.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 Chriſt borne, 7. Shepheards, 8. Chriſt circum<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ciſed, 22. <hi>Simeon,</hi> 25. <hi>Anna,</hi> 36. Doctor, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 46.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 <hi>Baptiſt,</hi> 2. Asked, 10. Dove, 22. Genealogie, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 23</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 Tempt, 2. Preached, 14. Rejected, 24. Spirit, 33. Feaver, 39. Healed all, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 40.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 5 Taught, 3. Fiſhers, 5. Leper, 12. Palſie, 18. <hi>Le<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>vi,</hi> 27. Faſting, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 33.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 6 Sabbath, 1. Prayer, 12. Twelve, 13. Healed, 17. Bleſſed, 20. Love, 27. Lend, 34. Mote, 41. Tree, 43. Rocke, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 48.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 7 Centurion, 2. <hi>Naim,</hi> 11. <hi>Iohn,</hi> 19. Reed, 24. Prepared, 32. <hi>Simon, Verſ.</hi> 36.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 8 Women, 2. Seed, 5. Candle, 16. Mother, 19. Storme, 23. Legion, 26. <hi>Iairus,</hi> 41. Iſſue, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 43.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 9 Twelve ſent, 2. <hi>Herod,</hi> 7. 5000, 14. Foretold, 22. Croſſe, 23. Transfigured, 28. Spirit, 39. Foretold, 44. Greateſt, 46. For us, 50. Fire, 54. Follow, 57. Chriſts Plough, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 62.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 10 Seventy, 1. Duſt, 11. <hi>Corazin,</hi> 13. Rejoyce, 20. Bleſſed, 23. Lawyer, 25. Neighbour, 29. <hi>Mat<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>thew, Verſ.</hi> 38.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 11 Lords Prayer, 2. Aske, 9. <hi>Belzebub,</hi> 14. Strong 21. Paps, 27. <hi>Ionas,</hi> 29. Light, 34. Waſh, 38. Roots, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 42.</item>
               <pb n="74" facs="tcp:9621:39"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 12 Hid, 2. Feare, 4. Confeſſe, 8. Covetouſneſſe, 15 Barnes, 18. Lillies, 27. Flocke, 32. Loynes, 35. Servants, 37. Fire, 49. Sky, 54. Adverſary, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 58.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 13 Repent, 3. Fig-tree, 6. 18 yeares, 11. Sabbath, 14. Two Parables, 18. Gate, 24. Fox, 32. <hi>Ieru<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſalem, Verſ.</hi> 34.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 14 Pit, 3. Gueſts, 8. Poore, 12. Supper, 16. Croſſe, 26. Build, 28. Salt, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 34.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 15 One hundred Sheepe, 4. Ioy, 7. Two Sons, 12. Prodigall, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 13.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 16 Steward, 1. Mammon, 9. Violence, 10. Di<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>vorce, 15. Glutton, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 19.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 17 Offences, 1. Faith, 6. Vnprofitable, 10. Tenne Lepers, 12. <hi>Noah,</hi> 26. <hi>Lots</hi> wife, 32. Eagles, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 37.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 18 Iudge, 2. Publican, 13. Children, 15. Cammell, 25. <hi>Peter,</hi> 28. Fore-tell, 31. Blind, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 35.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 19 <hi>Zacheus,</hi> 2. Ten pounds, 13. Colt, 30. Stones cry, 40. A trench, 43. Temple, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 45.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 20 Authority, 2. Vineyard, 9. Stone, 17. Tribute, 22. Reſurrection, 27. <hi>David,</hi> 41. Robes, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 46.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 21 Two mites, 2. Signes, 7. Laſt day, 25. Watch <hi>Verſ.</hi> 36.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 22 <hi>Matthew,</hi> 26. Greateſt, 27. <hi>Marke,</hi> 14. <hi>Iohn, Verſ.</hi> 13.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 23 <hi>Matth.</hi> 27. <hi>Mark,</hi> 15. <hi>Iohn, Verſ.</hi> 18, 19.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 24 <hi>Matth.</hi> 28. <hi>Emmaus,</hi> 13. Eate, 43. Aſcended, 51. <hi>Marke,</hi> 16. <hi>Iohn, Verſ.</hi> 20.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <pb n="75" facs="tcp:9621:39"/>
               <head>IOHN.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 LIght, 4. <hi>Iohn,</hi> 6. Lambe, 29. <hi>Andrew,</hi> 40. <hi>Ce<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>phas,</hi> 42. <hi>Philip,</hi> 43. <hi>Nathaniel, Verſ.</hi> 45.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 Cana, 1. Temple, 14. Paſſeover, 13. Signe, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 <hi>Nicodemus,</hi> 1. Serpent, 14. Light, 19. Bride, 29 Seale, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 33.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 Samaritane, 7. Reape, 38. Rulers ſonne, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 46.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 5 Eight and thirty yeares, 5. Sabbath, 9. Father, 17. Graves, 28. Foure witneſſes, 31. Scripture 39. <hi>Moſes, Verſ.</hi> 46.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 6 Five thouſand fed, 10. King, 15. Sea, 18. Bread. 32. Goe backe, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 66.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 7 Brethren, 3. Murmure, 12. Divell, 20. His houre, 30. Thirſt, 37. <hi>Nicodemus, Verſ.</hi> 50.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 8 Adultereſſe, 3. Witneſſe, 18. Father, 16. Free<g ref="char:punc">▪</g> 32. <hi>Abraham,</hi> 37. Divell, 44. I am, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 58.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 9 Borne blinde, 1. Parents, 18. Excommunicate, 34. Iudgement, 39. Blind, 40. Wee ſee, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 41.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 10 Shepheard, 2. Diviſion, 19. Tell us, 24. Stones, 31. Gods, 35. Eſcaped, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 39.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 11 <hi>Lazarus,</hi> 1. Twelve houres, 9. <hi>Caiphas,</hi> 49. <hi>E<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>phraim,</hi> 54. Paſſeover, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 55.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 12 Oyntment, 3. <hi>Hoſanna,</hi> 13. Greekes, 20. Voyce, 28. <hi>Iſaiah,</hi> 38. Light, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 46.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 13 Waſhed, 5. If yee know, 17. Receive me, 20. Betray, 21. Sop, 26. Love, 24. Glorified, 31. Cock crew, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 38.</item>
               <pb n="76" facs="tcp:9621:40"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 14 Manſions, 2. Way, 6. Father, 7. Aske, 13. Love 15. Comforter, 26. Goe away, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 28.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 15 Vine, 1. Love, 9. Friends, 13. Aske, 16. Not of world, 19. Hate me, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 25.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 16 Spirit, 7. Reprove, 8. Little while, 16. Aske, 23. Scattered, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 32.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 17 CHRISTS Prayer, 1. Not for world, 9. One with us, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 21.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 18 <hi>Chriſt</hi> betrayed, 2. <hi>Peter,</hi> 10. <hi>Pilate,</hi> 29. <hi>Ba<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>rabas, Verſ.</hi> 40.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 19 Condemned, 6. Crucified, 18. Mother, 25. Pier<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ced, 34. Buried, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 40.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 20 Reſurrection, 1. <hi>Mary,</hi> 11. <hi>Thomas,</hi> 24. Ma<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ny ſignes, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 30.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 21 Fiſhing, 3. Chriſt eateth, 13. <hi>Simon,</hi> 15. Not dye, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 23.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>ACTS.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap,</hi> 1 BAptiz'd, 5. Aſcenſion, 9. Perſons, 15. <hi>Iu<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>das,</hi> 16. <hi>Mathias, Verſ.</hi> 23.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap,</hi> 2 Cloven tongues, 3. <hi>Peters</hi> Sermon, 14. <hi>Ioel,</hi> 16 <hi>David,</hi> 25. Prickt in heart, 37. Common, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 44.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap,</hi> 3 Cripple, 1. Marvell, 12. Repent, 19. Times of refreſhing, 21. Prophet, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 22.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap,</hi> 4 5000, 4. Obey God, 19. Prayed, 24. Place ſhaken, 31. All common, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 32.</item>
               <pb n="79" facs="tcp:9621:40"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap,</hi> 5 <hi>Ananias,</hi> 1. Signes, 12. Priſoned, 18. <hi>Ga<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>maliel,</hi> 34. Beaten, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 40.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap,</hi> 6 Seven Deacons, 5. Prieſts beleeved, 7. <hi>Ste<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>phen</hi> did wonders, 8. Face of Angell, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 13.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap,</hi> 7 <hi>Stephens</hi> Sermon, 2. <hi>Aegypt,</hi> 11. <hi>Moſes,</hi> 20. Prophet, 37. Stiffe-necked, 51. Stoned, 58. Prayed, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 60.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap,</hi> 8 <hi>Saul,</hi> 1. <hi>Philip,</hi> 3. <hi>Simon,</hi> 9. <hi>Peter,</hi> 14. Eu<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>nuch, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 27.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap,</hi> 9 <hi>Sauls</hi> converſion, 4. Basket, 25. <hi>Tarſus,</hi> 30. Reſt, 31. <hi>Aeneas,</hi> 33. <hi>Dorcas, Verſ.</hi> 36.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap,</hi> 10 <hi>Cornelius,</hi> 1. <hi>Peters</hi> trance, 9. Sermon, 34. Holy Ghoſt, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 44.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap,</hi> 11 <hi>Peters</hi> Apologie, 4. <hi>Antioch,</hi> 19. <hi>Saul</hi> a whole yeere, 26. Firſt Chriſtians, 26. <hi>Aga<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>bus, Verſ.</hi> 28.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap,</hi> 12 <hi>Herod,</hi> 1. <hi>Iames,</hi> 2. <hi>Peter,</hi> 3. Iron gate, 10. <hi>Rhode,</hi> 13. <hi>Herods</hi> oration, 21. Wormes, 23. <hi>Sauls</hi> returne, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 25.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap,</hi> 13 Faſted, 2. <hi>Elymas,</hi> 8. <hi>Iohn,</hi> 13. <hi>Anti<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>och,</hi> 14. <hi>David,</hi> 34. Gentiles, 46. Belee<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ved, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 48.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap,</hi> 14 <hi>Iconium,</hi> 1. <hi>Lyſtra,</hi> 5. Gods, 11. <hi>Paul</hi> ſtoned, 19. Returned, 21. Elders, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 23.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap,</hi> 15 Circumciſion, 1. Apoſtles decrees, 22. Con<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tention between <hi>Paul</hi> and <hi>Barnabas, Verſ.</hi> 39.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap,</hi> 16 <hi>Timotheus,</hi> 1. <hi>Pauls</hi> journeyes, 8. <hi>Philippi,</hi> 12. <hi>Lydia,</hi> 14. Iayler, 27. Romanes, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 37.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap,</hi> 17 <hi>Theſſalonica,</hi> 1. Chiefe, 4. <hi>Iaſon,</hi> 7. <hi>Berea,</hi> 10. Athens, 15. Vnknowne god, 23. Re<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>pent, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 30.</item>
               <pb n="80" facs="tcp:9621:41"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap,</hi> 18 <hi>Corinth,</hi> 1. <hi>Aquila,</hi> 2. <hi>Gallio,</hi> 12. Churches, 22. <hi>Apollos.</hi>
               </item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap,</hi> 19 Holy Ghoſt, 2. <hi>Epheſus,</hi> two yeeres, 10. Ex<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>orciſt, 13. Bookes, 19. <hi>Diana, Verſ.</hi> 24.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap,</hi> 20 Iourneyes, 1. <hi>Eutychus,</hi> 9. <hi>Melitus,</hi> 15. See face no more, 25. Wolves, 29. Word of grace, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 32.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap,</hi> 21 Iourneyes, 1. <hi>Agabus,</hi> 10. Ieruſalem, 17. Vow 23. Vproare, 27. Bound, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 33.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap,</hi> 22 <hi>Pauls</hi> defence, 1. Of his converſion, 3. Eſca<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ped being a Romane, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 25.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap,</hi> 23 Councell, 1. Whited wall, 3. I am a Phariſie, 6. Be of good cheere, 11. Conſpiracy by forty, 12. Sent to Faelix, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 24.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap,</hi> 24 <hi>Tertullus,</hi> 1. <hi>Pauls</hi> anſwer, 10. Conſcience, 16. <hi>Faelix</hi> trembles, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 25.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap,</hi> 25 <hi>F<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                        <desc>•</desc>
                     </gap>ſtus,</hi> 1. Appeale, 10. <hi>Agrippa, Verſ.</hi> 13.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap,</hi> 26 Before <hi>Agrippa,</hi> 1. Of his convenſion made, 24. Almoſt, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 29.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap,</hi> 27 Sayling, 2. Angell, 23. Perſons 276, 27. Shipwracke, 4<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>. Safe, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 44.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap,</hi> 28 <hi>Melita,</hi> 1. Viper, 3. All healed, 9. Rome, 14: Two yeeres, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 30.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <pb n="81" facs="tcp:9621:41"/>
               <head>ROMANS.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 MVtuall Faith, 13. Goſpell, 16. Godhead; 20. Vile affection, 26. Naturall man his ſinnes, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 29.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 Inexcuſable, 1. Treaſure, 6. No repſect, 11. Law, 12. Iewes, 17. Sinnes, <hi>ibid.</hi> Iew with<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>in, 29. Circumciſion, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 25.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 Iewes advantage, 1. All guilty, 9. Righteouſ<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>neſſe by faith, 22. Iuſtified, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 28.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 <hi>Abraham,</hi> 1. <hi>David</hi> juſtified, 6. Circumciſion, 9. Faith 16. Imputed for righteouſneſſe, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 22.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 5 Fruits of ſaith, 1. Reconciled, 10. By one man ſinne, 12. Grace abounds, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 15.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 6 Sanctification, 1. Dead with Chriſt. 3. Sinne raigneth, 12. Servant of ſin, 16. Wages. <hi>Verſ.</hi> 23.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 7 Law, 2. Luſt, 7. Spirituall battaile, 9. Will is preſent, 18. O wretched man, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 24.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 8 Comfort over corruption, 1. Fleſh, 5. Spirit, 5. Abba, 15. Affliction, 18. Creature, 19. Tri<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>umph, 31. Separate, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 35.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 9 Accurſed, 3. <hi>Iſrael,</hi> 6. <hi>Iacob,</hi> 13. <hi>Pharaoh,</hi> 17. Potter, 21. Remnant, 27. Stone, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 33.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 10 Zeale, 2. Not of workes, 5. Righteouſnes of faith, 6. Faith by hearing, 17. <hi>Iſaiah, Verſ.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 11 Caſting off the Iewes, 1. Election, 4. Saved, 7. Faſt, 12. Call of Gentiles, 13. Olive, 17. Iewes againe, 24. Depth, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 39.</item>
               <pb n="82" facs="tcp:9621:42"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 12 Living ſacrifice, 1. Members, 4. Holy duties, 9. If thine enemy, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 13 Obedience to Rulers, 1. Love, 8. Might, 12. No riot, 13. Put on Chriſt, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 14.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 14 Indifferents, 2. Iudge not, 4. Not to of<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>fend our brother, 13. Vncleane, 15. Doubt<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ing, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 23.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 15 Pleaſe, 2. Scripture, 4. Gentiles, 9. God of hope, 13. Illyricum, <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>9. Spaine, 24. Pray for me, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 30.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 16 Salutations, 1. Diviſions, 17. Simple to evill, 19. God onely wiſe, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 27.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>1. CORINTHIANS.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 RIch, 5. Called, 9. Diviſions, 11. Baptize, 14. Fooliſhneſſe, 18. Baſe, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 28.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 Wiſdome of men, 4. Spirit, 10. Naturall men, 14. Spirituall, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 15.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 Carnall, 1. Building, 9. Temple of God, 16. Wiſe, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 Stewards, 1. Iudge nothing, 5. Off-ſcouring, 13. Fathers, 15. Puffed up, 18. Rod, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 22.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 5 Inceſt, 1. Old Leven, 7. Eat not, 11. Iudge within, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 12.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 6 Goe to Law, 1. Iudge, 2. No fornication, 9. All lawfull, 12. Harlot, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 15.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 7 Marriage, 1. Defraud not, 5. Abide in calling.
<pb n="83" facs="tcp:9621:42"/> 17. Virgins, 25. Vſe world, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 31.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 8 Idoll, 1. Know nothing, 2. One God, 6. Not to offend brother, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 9.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 9 Seale of Apoſtleſhip, 2. Live of the Goſpell, 14. Preach, 16. All to all, 22. So run, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 26.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 10 Enſample, 6. Tentation, 13. Communion, 16. Devils, 20. Conſcience, 25. Glory, 31. Of<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>fence, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 32.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 11 Covered, 4. Lords Supper abuſed, 17. Exa<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mine, 8. Iudged of the Lord, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 31.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 12 Divers gifts, 4. Not one member, 14. Apo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtles, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 28.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 13 Love, 4. In part, 9. As a Childe, 11. Charity greateſt, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 13.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 14 Propheſie, 1. Tongues, 4. Amen, 16. Mad, 23. Prophets, 29. Women ſilent, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 34.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 15 Reſurrection, 4. Leaſt of Apoſtles, 9. God all, 28. Soweſt. 36. All changed, 51. Sting, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 55.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 16 Collection, 1. Doore, 9. Be ſtrong, 13. Ana<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>thema, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 22.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>2. CORINTHIANS.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 COnſolation, 4. Delivered, 10. Conſcience, 12. Yea and Amen, 20. E<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>rneſt of the Spirit, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 22.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 Griefe, 1. Forgive, 7. Satan, 11. Savor of death, 16. Word, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 17.</item>
               <pb n="84" facs="tcp:9621:43"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 Epiſtle, 2. Miniſtery of the Spirit, 6. Vaile, 13. Glaſſe, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 Goſpell hid, 3. Not forſaken, 9. Light afflic<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tion, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 17.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 5 Houſe, 1. Earneſt, 5. Iudgment, 10. Dy<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ed for all, 15. New cr<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>ature, 17. Reconci<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>led, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 6 Grace in vaine, 1. In ſtripes, 5. <hi>Belial,</hi> 15. My Sonnes, 18, &amp;c.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 7 Cleanſe, 1. Godly ſorrow, 10. Boaſted, 14. I have confidence in, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 16.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 8 <hi>Macedonia,</hi> 1. Contribution, 7. Willing minde, 12. <hi>Titus,</hi> 16. Glory of Chriſt, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 23.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 9 <hi>Achaia,</hi> 2. Reape ſparingly, 6. Chearefull gi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ver, 7. Thanks, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 11.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 10 Bold, 1. Weapons, 4. Boaſt, 8. Letters, 10. Our meaſure, 13. Not boaſting, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 15.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 11 Virgin, 2. Another Goſpell, 4. Abaſe, 7. Preach freely, 7. Transforme, 14. Boaſting, 17. <hi>Pauls</hi> affliction, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 22.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 12 Revelations, 1. Buffet, 7. Infirmities, 10. Not burdenſome, 13. Debate, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 13 Chriſt not weake, 3. Examine, 5. Your per<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>fection, 9. Holy kiſſe, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 12.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <pb n="85" facs="tcp:9621:43"/>
               <head>To the GALATIANS.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 ANother Goſpell, 6. Not of man, 11. Went to <hi>Arabia,</hi> 17. Vnknowne, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 22.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 <hi>Titus,</hi> 3. Right hands, 9. Diſſembling, 11. Faith, 16. Chriſt liveth, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 O fooliſh, 1. Iuſtification, 8. Chriſt a curſe, 13. Covenant, 15. Law a Schoolemaſter, 24. Faith. 16. <hi>Verſ.</hi> 26.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 Heire, 1. <hi>Abba,</hi> 6. Elements, 9. Pluck out your eyes, 15. Chriſt be formed, 19. <hi>Agar, Verſ.</hi> 24.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 5 Circumciſion, 2. Ye did run well, 7. Works of fleſh, 19. And ſpirit, 22. Who be Chriſts, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 
                  <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>4.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 6 Burden, 2. Sowing, 7. Glory in the Cro<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                     <desc>••</desc>
                  </gap>e, 14. New creature, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 15.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>To the EPHESIANS.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 CHoſen, 4. Myſtery, 9. Sealed, 13. Hope of <gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>is calling, 18. Hea<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="1 letter">
                     <desc>•</desc>
                  </gap>, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 22.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 Dead, 1. Saved by grace, 5. Aliens, 12. Both one, 14. Corner-ſtone, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 Gentiles, 1. Leaſt, 8. I bow my knees, 14. Length and bredth, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 Vnity, 3. Miniſtry, 12. The old man, 22. New,
<pb n="86" facs="tcp:9621:44"/> 24. Duties, 25. Anger, 26. Kind, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 32.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 5 Ieſting, 4. Once darkneſſe, 8. Light, 13. As wiſe, 15. Wives. 22. Husbands, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 25.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 6 Children. 1. Servants, 5. Spirituall armour, 10. Prayer, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 18.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>To the PHILIPPIANS.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 THankes. 3. His prayer, 4. Bonds, 7. Chriſt is preacht, 15. Diſſolved, 22. Converſati<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>on, 27. To ſuffer, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 29.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 Vnity, 2. Lowly as Chriſt, 5. Knee, 10. Will and doe, 13. Offered, 17. <hi>Timothy,</hi> 19. <hi>Epaphro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ditus, Verſ.</hi> 24.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 Dogs. 2. Loſſe, 7. Pride, 14. Belly their god, 19. Body changed, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 21.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 Rejoyce, 4. Good report. 8. I can want, 12. Communicate, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 15.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>To the COLOSSIANS.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 THankes, 3. Prayer, 9. Chriſt, 13. Reconci<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>led, 20. Myſtery, 26. Gentiles, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 27.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 Conflict, 1. Rudiments, 8. All in Chriſt, 9. Hand-writing, 14. Angels, 18, Touch not, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 21.</item>
               <pb n="87" facs="tcp:9621:44"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 Things above, 1. Put off, 8. Put on, 10. Hymms, 16. Wives, 18. Children, 20. Servants, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 22.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 Maſters, 1. Pray, 2. Salt, 6. <hi>Tychius,</hi> 7. <hi>Luke,</hi> 14. Epaphras, 12. Salute, 15. Laodicea, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 16.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>1. THESSALONIANS.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 YOur faith, 3. Election, 4. Enſample, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 7.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 No cloake, 5. Nurſe, 7. How holily, 10. Word, 13. Their ſufferings, 14. Our crowne, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 19.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 Afflictions, 3. We live, 8. See your face, 10. God direct, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 11.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 Your ſanctification, 3. Love, 9. Reſurrection, 13. Archangell, 16. Dead riſe, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 17.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 5 Day of the Lord, 2. Sleepe, 6. Know them, 12. Exhort, 14. Rejoyce, 16. Quench not, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 19.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>2. THESSALONIANS.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 FAith grow, 3. Sufferings, 4. In flaming fire, 8. We pray, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 11.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 Man of ſinne, 3. Deluſion, 11. Choſen, 13. Tra<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>dition, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 15.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 Vnreaſonable, 2. Inordinate, 6. Admoniſh, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 15.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <pb n="88" facs="tcp:9621:45"/>
               <head>1. TIMOTHY.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 ENd of law, 5. Lawleſſe, 9. Ignorantly, 13. Charge, 18. Hymeneus, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 Prayers, 1. Ranſome for all, 6. Women, 9. Subject, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 11.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 Biſhops, 2. Deacons, 8. Gods houſe, 15. My<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſtery, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 16.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 Latter times, 1. All ſanctified, 5. Godlines, 8. Doctrine, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 13.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 5 Widdowes, 3. Elders, 17. Lay hands, 22. Wine, 23. Sinnes, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 24.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 6 Servants, 1. Proud, 4. Godlineſſe, 6. Will be, 9. Fight, 12. Charge rich, 17. Babling, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 20.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>2. TIMOTHY.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 TEares, 4. <hi>Lois,</hi> 5. Not aſhamed, 8. Doctrine, 13. <hi>Oneſiphorus, Verſ.</hi> 16.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 Strive, 5. To ſuffer, 9. Dividing, 15. Canker, 17. Veſſels, 20. Not ſtrive, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 24.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 Laſt dayes, 1. Women, 6. <hi>Iannes,</hi> 8. Perſecu<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tion, 11. All Scripture, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 16.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 Breach, 2. Itching eares, 3. A crowne, 8. <hi>Do<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mas,</hi> 12. All forſooke, 16. Lyon, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 17.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <pb n="89" facs="tcp:9621:45"/>
               <head>TO TITVS.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 BIſhop, 7. Cretians, 12. All pure, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 15.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 Young and old, 2. Patternes, 7. Servants, 9. Grace of God, 11. Chriſt, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 14.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 Subject, 1. Deceived, 3. Regenerate, 5. Here<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tick, 10. <hi>Artemas, <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 12.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>TO PHILEMON.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 HIs Love, 5. <hi>Oneſimus,</hi> 10. Lodging, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 22.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>To the HEBREWES.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 CHriſt above Angels, 4. His God-head, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 8.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 Goſpell, 3. Chriſt man, 6. Suffered, 9. Brethren, 12. Deliver us, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 15.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 As <hi>Moſes,</hi> 3. Houſe, 4. Evill heart, 12. Har<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>den not, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 15.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 His reſt, 1. Word quicke, 12. Throne of grace, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 16.</item>
               <pb n="90" facs="tcp:9621:46"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 5 High Prieſt, 1. Called, 4. Milke, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 12.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 6 Principles, 1. Fall away, 4. Earth, 7. God ſware, 13. Hope-Anker, 19. Chriſts Prieſt-hood, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 7 <hi>Melchiſedec,</hi> 1. Tythes, 5. With oath for ever, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 24.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 8 True Tabernacle, 2. New Covenant, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 8.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 9 Firſt Tabernacle, 1. Owne blood, 12. Teſta<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ment, 16. Once offered, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 28.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 10 Volume, 7. One Sacrifice, 12. Faith, 22. Sin willingly, 26. Affliction, 32. Draw backe, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 38.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 11 By faith, 2. Stoned, 37. Not perfect, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 40.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 12 Runne, 1. All chaſtiſed, 6. <hi>Eſau</hi> 16. Sion, 22. Shaken, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 26.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 13 Marriage, 4. Altar, 10. Doe good, 16. Obey, 17. Pray, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 18.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>IAMES.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 PAtience, 3. Wavering, 6. Rich, 10. Tempted, 13. Begat, 18. Wrath, 19. Glaſſe, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 23.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 Poore, 2. Guilty of all, 10. Vaine faith, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 14.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 Tongue, 5. Wiſdome, 13. Earthly, 15. Hea<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>venly, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 17.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 Warres, 1. Adulterers, 4. Devill, 7. Mourne, 9. Law, 11. If God will, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 14.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 5 Ruſt, 3. Patient, 7. Sweare, 12. Pray, 13. Con<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>feſſe fault, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 16.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <pb n="91" facs="tcp:9621:46"/>
               <head>1. PETER.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 BLeſſed, 3. Inheritance, 4. Tryalls, 7. Pro<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>phets, 10. Holy, 13. Lambe, 19. Borne againe, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 23.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 Milke, 2. Stone, 4. People, 9. Pilgrims, 11. King, 13. Servant, 18. Chriſt, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 21.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 Wives, 1. Love, 8. Life, 10. Suffer, 14. <hi>No<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ah,</hi> 20. Baptiſme, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 21.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 No longer, 2. Riot, 4. End, 7. Watch, 7. Stew<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ards, 10. Fiery tryall, 12. Scarce ſaved, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 5 Elders, 1. Not Lords, 3. Submit, 5. Care, 7. Lyon, 8. Stabliſh, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 10.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>2. PETER.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 ALL in Chriſt, 3. Election ſure, 10. Put in remembrance, 12. Day-ſtarre, 19. Mo<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ved, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 21.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 Falſe teachers, 1. Gods judgments, 5. Lot, 7. Spots, 13. <hi>Balaam,</hi> 15. End worſe, 20. Sow, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 22.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 Scoffers, 3. All burnt, 10. <hi>Paul,</hi> 15. Grow in Grace, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 18.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <pb n="92" facs="tcp:9621:47"/>
               <head>1. IOHN.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 VVOrd of Life, 1. Fellowſhip, 3. Walke in light, 7. No ſinne, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 8.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 Advocate, 1. No new command, 7. Love, 10 Fa<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>thers, 13. World, 15. Antichriſt, 18. Vnction, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 Like Chriſt, 2. Sinneth not, 6. <hi>Cain,</hi> 12. Love, 14. Heart condemne, 20. Aske, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 22.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 Try ſpirits, 1. World, 5. Love of Brethren, 7. Gods love, 9. Spirit, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 13.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 5 Borne of God, 1. Three witneſſes, 7. Lyer, 10. Aske, 14. Sinne unto death, <hi>Verſe.</hi> 16.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>2. IOHN.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 VVAlke in truth, 2. Deceivers, 7. Loſe not, 8. God ſpyed, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 11.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>3. IOHN.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap<g ref="char:punc">▪</g>
                  </hi> 1 VVAlke in truth, 2. Diotrephes, 9. Deme<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>trius, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſe.</hi> 12.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <pb n="93" facs="tcp:9621:47"/>
               <head>IVDE.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 FAith, 3. Vngodly, 4. Angels, 6. <hi>Michael,</hi> 9. Spots, 12. <hi>Enoch,</hi> 14. Mockers, 18. Faith, 20. Fire, <hi>Verſ.</hi> 23.</item>
            </list>
            <list>
               <head>REVELATION.</head>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 1 BLeſſed, 3. Alpha, 8. Seven Churches, 11- Sonne of man, 13. Keyes of Hell, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 2 Epheſus, 1. Firſt love, 4. Smerna, 8. Tenne dayes, 10. Pergamus, 12. Antipas, 13. Thya<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>tira, 18. Iezabel, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 3 Sardis, 1. Few names, 4. Philadelphia, 7. Open doore, 8. Laodicea, 14. Warme, 16. Supper, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 4 Throne, 2. Foure beaſts, 6. Twenty foure El<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ders, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 10.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 5 Booke. 1. Lambe, 6. Song. 9. Every creature, 12. Bleſſing, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 13.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 6 Firſt ſeale, 1. Horſes, 4. Soules, 9. Robes. 10. Scroll, 14. Fall on us, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 16.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 7 Number of ſealed, 4. White Robes, 9. All teares, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 17.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 8 Seventh ſeale, 1. Cenſer, 3. Foure trumpets, 7. Wormwood, 11. Woe, woe, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 13.</item>
               <pb n="94" facs="tcp:9621:48"/>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 9 Locuſts, 3. Shape, 7. Apollyon, 11. Angell, 13. Army, 16. Repented not, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 20.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 10 Seven thunders, 4. No time, 6. Eat booke, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 9.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 11 Reed, 1. Two witneſſes, 3. Killed. 7. Recei<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ved, 11. Seventh Angell, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 15.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 12 Woman, 2. Dragon, 3. Satan caſt, 9. F<gap reason="illegible" resp="#KEYERS" extent="2 letters">
                     <desc>••</desc>
                  </gap>ud, 15. Warre, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 17.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 13 Beaſt, 1. Overcome, 7. Second beaſt, 11. I<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>mage. 14. Marke of Beaſt, 16. Sixe hundred threeſcore and ſixe, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 18.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 14 144000, 1. Lambe, 4. <hi>Babylon</hi> is falne, 8. Bleſſed, 13. Sickle, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 14.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 15 Sea of Glaſſe, 2. Song of <hi>Moſes,</hi> 3. Seven Vi<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>als, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 7.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 16 Seven Plagues, 1. Repented not, 9. Eight Frogs, 13. Babylon, 19. Great haile, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 21.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 17 Whore of Rome, 1. Beaſt was, 8. Ten Kings, 12. Lambe ſhall overcome, 14. Burne her, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 16.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 18 Babylon burnt, 2. Come out, 4. Alas, 10, Her riches, 12. Rejoyce, 20. Her ſinne, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 21.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 19 Hallelu-jah, 1. Marriage of Lambe, 7. Worſhip God, 10. Chriſt overcomes all, 11. Beaſt take<g ref="char:cmbAbbrStroke">̄</g>, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 20</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 20 Satan bound, 2. Soules lived, 4. Satan looſed, 7. 1000. yeares, 7. Laſt judgment, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 12.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 21 All new, 1 Lyers, 8. Bride, 9. Holy City, 10. No Sunne, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 23.</item>
               <item>
                  <hi>Chap.</hi> 22 Waters, 1. Tree of life, 2. No night, 5. Wor<g ref="char:EOLhyphen"/>ſhip God, 9. Bleſſed, 14. Come, 17. Adde, <hi>
                     <g ref="char:V">Ʋ</g>erſ.</hi> 18.</item>
            </list>
            <trailer>FINIS.</trailer>
            <pb facs="tcp:9621:48"/>
         </div>
      </body>
   </text>
</TEI>
